1,800	O
strong-dollar	O
1,803	O
1,806	O
Larsen	I-PER
hanging	O
five-nation	O
LAST	O
Moreira	I-PER
refunding	O
Western	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
crossbar	O
Caen	I-ORG
Euro	I-MISC
109.36	O
Jornada	I-ORG
co-operation	O
Valle	I-PER
S-1	I-MISC
bringing	O
.578	O
grueling	O
wooden	O
.573	O
.571	O
.576	O
.574	O
.575	O
south-west	O
273	O
FIGURES	O
275	O
277	O
278	O
279	O
errors	O
Hamilton	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
replaced	O
PMC-Sierra	I-ORG
Croat	I-MISC
zlotys	O
10700	O
Parmalat	I-ORG
affiliated	O
One-year	I-MISC
kids	O
MATCHES	O
climbed	O
controversy	O
Jewell	I-PER
Shelbourne	I-ORG
golden	O
projection	O
Harvey	I-PER
stern	O
prospector	O
NSDAP-AO	I-ORG
reasserting	O
Zhirinovsky	I-PER
LOUIS	I-ORG
meteorologist	O
5.13	O
Strobe	I-PER
5.15	O
circumstances	O
locked	O
Colombia	I-LOC	I-ORG
+525	O
Le	I-ORG	I-PER
La	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
Li	I-PER
American-style	I-MISC
Lu	I-PER
Ninth	I-ORG
want	O
absolute	O
LG	I-ORG
LE	I-ORG
SCORERS	O
LA	I-ORG
travel	O
cutback	O
LP	I-ORG
SURGERY	O
Teguh	I-ORG
L.	I-PER
wrong	O
RESERVES	O
CFO	O
Hoping	O
18th	O
Shimon	I-PER
JOBLESS	O
welcomed	O
Wills	I-PER
partnered	O
rewarded	O
welcomes	O
Abbott	I-PER
His	O
fix	O
Second-placed	O
Fax+44	O
omitted	O
3-0-15-0	O
Ferrigato	I-PER
Doohan	I-PER
Zinzan	I-PER
Hintsa	I-PER
HIGH	O
effects	O
dungeon-like	O
LECIVA	I-ORG
burial	O
39.	O
391	O
strips	O
396	O
395	O
398	O
Crowds	O
120,000	O
encourage	O
corrects	O
estimate	O
Nigel	I-PER
Ibrahimi	I-PER
ministries	O
disturbed	O
competed	O
shrugged-off	O
loudness	O
MCRAE	I-PER
Chants	O
cordoned-off	O
service	O
zinfandel	O
needed	O
horse-drawn	O
61.94	O
mutilated	O
Oracle	I-ORG
positively	O
Pvs	O
x-Club	I-ORG
35-year-old	O
274	O
feeling	O
SPEED	O
third-round	O
Chicago	I-LOC	I-ORG
AWARDED	O
406.6	O
dozen	O
affairs	I-ORG	O
Fontaine	I-ORG
paramedics	O
90.50	O
racers	O
Economic	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
They	O
Missionary	I-LOC
Stocher	I-PER
shipments	O
45th	O
committing	O
sugarcane	O
diminishing	O
mouth	O
2,500-seat	O
conceded	O
singer	O
300-club	O
scream	O
non-EU	I-MISC
saying	O
cheaply	O
Resources	I-ORG
REUTER	I-PER
Heinz-Harald	I-PER
Kamyshin	I-ORG
rice	O
Eilts	I-PER
plate	O
Tricks	I-PER
7-11	O
altogether	O
nicely	O
patch	O
Rio	I-LOC	I-ORG
Senegalese	I-MISC
Rig	I-ORG
cull	O
Anderson	I-PER
47-38	O
196.8	O
48th	O
deadpan	O
Heidrun	I-LOC
Guayana	I-ORG
ire	O
Advanced	I-ORG
discipline	O
extend	O
nature	O
70th	O
10.5-42.3	O
+12	O
+11	O
+17	O
veer	O
+19	O
heating	O
levitating	O
high-yielding	O
southeastern	O
eradicate	O
Resalat	I-ORG
11.16	O
Reuter	I-ORG	I-PER
11.12	O
82-96F	O
blonde	O
3.83	O
3.87	O
3.85	O
union	O
3.89	O
HINA	I-ORG
.	O
much	O
+3.06	O
tallest	O
Remington	I-MISC
Arnaud	I-PER
Tutsis	I-MISC
Donovan	I-PER
doubts	O
spin	O
bargain-hunters	O
employ	O
deferring	O
eighteen	O
London-based	O
breakfast	O
memorial	O
BSE-infected	I-MISC
13.18	O
split	O
codename	O
Allenby	I-LOC	I-PER
Maybe	O
workforce	O
marched	O
Bentsen	I-PER
Muralitharan	I-PER
Dietsch	I-PER
Martyn	I-PER
Kaucuk	I-ORG
academic	O
corporate	O
CYPRIEN	I-PER
Rapid	I-ORG
Truth	I-ORG
Gulyayeva	I-PER
Happy	O
ham	O
out-of-town	O
Oscar	I-PER
had	O
Baghdad	I-LOC
has	O
Spence	I-PER
municipal	O
survival	O
REQUEST	O
anti-Semitic	I-MISC
shadow	O
+1,161	O
Brenda	I-PER
NORTHAMPTON	I-LOC
festivities	O
Aranosian	I-PER
Pentagon	I-ORG
Swedish	I-MISC
Abyss	I-PER
beneficial	O
crowd	O
crown	O
begin	O
captive	O
Between	O
52nd	O
Susana	I-PER
bottom	O
inhuman	O
plucked	O
*INDICES	O
Ileana	I-PER
Buhner	I-PER
Seve	I-PER
pharaoh	O
starring	O
IBCA	I-ORG
Falkir	I-ORG
benched	O
Fredericks	I-PER
pre-tax	O
Abimael	I-PER
administer	O
Aaron	I-PER
outscored	O
CARLING	I-PER
Endt	I-PER
Versace	I-PER
Moengo	I-LOC
raped	O
PUK-KDP	I-MISC
Palestinian-ruled	I-MISC
Lapentti	I-PER
duel	O
County	I-MISC	B-MISC	I-ORG	I-LOC
complications	O
pesos	O
smashed	O
Jays	I-ORG
passenger	O
disgrace	O
Sentiment	O
Inderfurth	I-PER
HEALED	O
Talen	I-PER
eventual	O
Sovetov	I-ORG
1995-96	O
role	O
OHIO	I-ORG
roll	O
5/1/98-02	O
E	O
Capiot	I-PER
Melbourne	I-LOC	I-ORG
intent	O
variable	O
explosions	O
Sudanese	I-MISC
Nouakchott	I-LOC
Encephalopathy	I-MISC
overturned	O
gown	O
chain	O
whoever	O
12.033	O
Ipswich	I-ORG
ballet	O
freelance	O
megawatts	O
Frentzen	I-PER
oversight	O
verbally	O
Palkhivala	I-PER
choice	O
Cronulla	I-ORG
gloomy	O
Bedouins	I-MISC
exact	O
minute	O
Tap	O
Tax	O
11-3/8	O
Tan	I-PER
Uralmash	I-ORG
Silvio	I-PER
meadow	O
Stefka	I-PER
Stefko	I-PER
hindered	O
Silvia	I-PER
M.	I-PER
M4	O
M1	O
M3	I-LOC
M2	O
Yedioth	I-ORG
5,200	O
celebrated	O
Magne	I-PER
ground	O
boost	O
Lopez	I-PER
drafted	O
climbs	O
honour	O
Mo	I-LOC	I-PER
Organisers	O
Bou	I-LOC
Dated	I-MISC
address	O
My	I-MISC	O
Webb	I-PER
plunges	O
Sitanyi	I-PER
LME	I-ORG
MT	B-LOC
accomplished	O
throughput	O
MS	O
ill-fated	O
Flach	I-PER
12-month	O
MX	I-ORG
influx	O
Lankan	I-MISC
Jone	I-ORG
Jonk	I-PER
Bob	I-PER
Davidson	I-PER
undergone	O
127.10	O
August	O
working	O
opposed	O
Bulldogs	I-ORG
Those	O
Klaus	I-PER
Bathel	I-PER
Artyom	I-PER
Standings	O
riders	O
Bart	I-PER
originally	O
abortion	O
Showers	O
following	O
Gadoon	I-LOC
Besirovic	I-PER
Makarova	I-PER
locks	O
litre	O
Goossens	I-PER
37-10-78-6	O
mid-September	O
thanking	O
extensions	O
STG	O
fueled	O
Rafiqul	I-PER
Corporate	O
LEAGUE	I-MISC	O
conscious	O
101-member	O
swollen	O
skirmish	O
pulled	O
Peterborough	I-ORG
years	O
Elias	I-PER
yeard	O
troubles	O
suspension	O
troubled	O
Arrigo	I-PER
fiscally-tight	O
civilian	O
five-metre	O
Iraqis	I-MISC
1,236.5	O
Deutsche	I-ORG	O
indigenous	O
drilling	O
Kemp	I-PER
unfruitful	O
24.8	O
materialized	O
24.6	O
105.07	O
Yellow	I-MISC	O
56rd	O
quarter	O
quartet	O
FIRST-ROUND	O
sponsor	O
entering	O
prudently	O
795	O
792	O
Michigan	I-LOC
Korean-related	I-MISC
seriously	O
trauma	O
2/32	O
incentives	O
complicated	O
Batistuta	I-PER
modest	O
Nuestra	I-LOC
aboard	O
Owens	I-PER
emotion	O
gunshot	O
saving	O
spoken	O
reprisal	O
one	O
punishable	O
Becej	I-ORG
Monday	O
LAKES	I-MISC
AGENT	O
15,286	O
4,200	O
Amica	I-ORG
Peeters	I-PER
785.00	O
specialists	O
surged	O
Fanton	I-PER
non-stop	O
Hubert	I-PER
illness	O
turned	O
locations	O
Field	I-LOC	I-PER
cigarettes	O
warriors	O
Alicia	I-PER
intends	O
Hall	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-PER
Halo	I-LOC
opposite	O
CSKA	I-ORG
Bari	I-ORG
Wong	I-PER
printed	O
Lands	O
LOME	I-LOC
Chonbuk	I-ORG
jitters	O
Chen	I-PER
Whitehurst	I-PER
mercenaries	O
10-0-59-1	O
Geelong	I-ORG
Sky	I-ORG
friction	O
Ethiopia	I-LOC
aggressive	O
reconciling	O
guarded	O
Assets	O
suitcases	O
1ama	I-PER
awaiting	O
quarter-finals	O
Ostrava	I-ORG
Facilities	I-ORG
pima	O
YES	O
ROLLS	O
vision	O
morose	O
JAKARTA	I-LOC
Mehrtens	I-PER
Worldwide	O
Pecs	I-ORG
Enqvist	I-PER
Jonah	I-PER
Rdainah	I-PER
're	O
Jonas	I-PER
Valkov	I-PER
enjoys	O
Mitsubishi	I-MISC	I-ORG
ex-dividend	O
Wachtel	I-PER
concentrated	O
Hathaway	I-ORG
Petrimex	I-ORG
s	O
workplace	O
212.00	O
collides	O
west	O
EUROSWISS	I-ORG
KDPI	I-ORG
collided	O
Correia	I-PER
wants	O
Tangible	O
formed	O
photos	O
tightened	O
MICKELSON	I-PER
former	O
Commander	O
newspaper	O
situation	O
Copland	I-MISC
Prem	I-ORG
U.S.-led	I-MISC
24.20	O
engaged	O
TRIPOLI	I-LOC
24.24	O
BBI-7.27	O
Clydebank	I-ORG
limping	O
engages	O
demolition	O
debilitating	O
verified	O
Taichung	I-ORG
managements	O
edged	O
Boavista	I-ORG
hideaway	O
defy	O
UTI	I-ORG
Tiantan	I-MISC
108.50	O
Clean	I-MISC	I-PER	O
agronomist	O
Pork	I-ORG
tracking	O
60,000	O
Port	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
persistently	O
NAC	I-ORG
being	O
NAN	I-ORG
Crossfire	I-MISC
Conservative	I-ORG	O
recycled	O
BOJ	I-ORG
grounded	O
overthrow	O
Guantanamo	I-LOC
Croatians	I-MISC
decomposed	O
gestures	O
traffic	O
preference	O
world	O
sensational	O
unrepentant	O
Sergio	I-PER
superiority	O
Man	I-ORG	I-PER
satisfactory	O
Khaled	I-PER
Beijing-backed	I-MISC
divine	O
cavity	O
918	O
911	I-MISC
Gartner	I-ORG
ANGOLA	I-LOC
Zyl	I-PER
leadership	O
Minardi	I-ORG
Revolution	I-MISC
financers	O
Cast	O
26-time	O
Goosen	I-PER
No	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
densely-populated	O
ROUTS	O
Finley	I-PER
NL	I-MISC
Durban	I-LOC
NO	O
NA	O
ND	I-ORG
8-0-33-0	O
NZ	I-LOC	I-ORG
sealed	O
NS	I-ORG
NT	I-MISC
NV	I-ORG
Hannover	I-LOC
heavily-mined	O
N.	I-PER
Tando	I-LOC
234,324	O
with	O
pull	O
monopoly	O
Rodriguez	I-PER
31.6	O
31.7	O
Platense	I-ORG
31.5	O
dirty	O
31.0	O
abuses	O
pulp	O
gratuitous	O
man-of-the-match	O
Airlines	I-ORG
watched	O
4,150	O
Real	I-ORG
RUNS	O
Lada	I-ORG
Burnley	I-ORG
1445	O
JONK	I-PER
Lady	I-LOC
passerby	O
Minutka	I-LOC
Bailundo	I-LOC
Housecall	I-ORG
3404.71	O
Heng	I-PER
tricks	O
dyed	O
consciences	O
10-30	O
caused	O
NABLUS	I-LOC
causes	O
photo-finish	O
riots	O
complete-game	O
Linford	I-PER
floated	O
square-jawed	O
floater	O
24th	O
4-7	O
small	O
sank	O
Gress	I-PER
USED	O
199	O
195	O
190	O
193	O
healed	O
past	O
19.	O
pass	O
Romina	I-PER
Grimwade	I-PER
investment	O
quicken	O
shockwave	O
clock	O
UNCHANGED	O
prevailed	O
Tanaki	I-PER
Ogilvy	I-ORG
Neiwand	I-PER
full	O
Baresi	I-PER
Abortion	I-ORG
Kostantin	I-PER
civilians	O
Kampfruf	I-ORG
Mercer	I-PER
Bonds	I-ORG	I-PER
experience	O
prior	O
TELO	I-ORG
followed	O
Kuwait	I-LOC
Filip	I-PER
Richmond	I-ORG
128-member	O
TRAINING	O
obstructing	O
Stranksy	I-PER
210,622	O
more	O
door	O
initiated	O
substances	O
0.958	O
company	O
corrected	O
tested	O
4,900	O
Spadea	I-PER
Celica	I-MISC
Raja	I-ORG
Capriati	I-PER
installing	O
learn	O
Raju	O
112.1-113.4	O
Glasgow	I-ORG
bonded	O
huge	O
dismissed	O
automotive	O
speedy	O
lanky	O
intended	O
Yussuf	I-PER
BLANTYRE	I-LOC
low-margin	O
Trailing	O
replied	O
installed	O
wide-ranging	O
resorts	O
paper	O
signs	O
smiling	O
BERNE	I-LOC
Durres	I-LOC
Valdo	I-PER
poetic	O
symptoms	O
Fisheries	I-ORG
bypass	I-MISC	O
3-0-17-0	O
Brussels	I-LOC
sauce	O
colleague	O
Lome	I-LOC
Hubner	I-PER
Berlanda	I-PER
Lomu	I-PER
58.00	O
Ameritech	I-ORG
Authority	I-ORG
shocking	O
chipping	O
524.2	O
Diyarbakir	I-LOC
operation	O
Nitto	I-PER
Jean-Denis	I-PER
denotes	O
occurs	O
Kubilay	I-PER
Ning	I-PER
pairs	O
MGR	O
CNIEC	I-ORG
MGT	O
Economist	O
precautionary	O
Dalai	I-PER
preservation	O
YANKEES	I-ORG
Catalan	I-MISC
Ligier	I-ORG
saint	O
rain-soaked	O
8,049	O
BELCHATOW	I-LOC
interviewed	O
interviewer	O
FRANKFURT	I-LOC
+0.4m	O
Hogg	I-PER
Stankov	I-ORG
getaway	O
charges	O
dismantling	O
organisations	O
reorganisation	O
NAIROBI	I-LOC
sell	O
Fook	I-PER
Food	I-ORG
extorted	O
heterosexual	O
also	O
recognizing	O
Othello	I-MISC
Ruhunu	I-ORG
Addis	I-LOC
CALLED	O
singles	O
virus	O
Presov	I-ORG
Grain	I-ORG	O
singled	O
understands	O
arson	O
seize	O
sometimes	O
Sharman	I-PER
barred	O
85-82	O
1687	O
TEST	O
Osteopathic	I-LOC
barrel	O
Scandanavia	O
VIENNA	I-LOC
Haj	I-PER
Hal	I-PER
Ham	I-ORG
Orr	I-PER
overwhelmed	O
occupation	O
careered	O
wraps	O
Jean-Philippe	I-PER
Base	I-LOC
Dirk	I-PER
indifference	O
columns	O
Wife	O
adventurers	O
sunny	O
BACK	O
remedy	O
Pvt	O
tanker	O
318	O
312	O
310	I-MISC	O
317	O
31.	O
EPA	I-ORG	O
15th	O
78th	O
Fulton	I-PER
Neil	I-PER
19.92	O
connection	O
eight-month-old	O
LISPI	I-MISC
Clyde	I-ORG
safer	O
suburbs	O
proprietor	O
Carl	I-PER
patrolled	O
Care	I-ORG
combatants	O
N.C.	I-LOC
infect	O
SELES	I-PER
pacemaker	O
consulate	O
Michel	I-PER
Marken	I-PER
GOAL	O
budget	O
pressed	O
32	O
cages	O
vol	O
binding	O
vow	O
Norwich	I-ORG
2.78	O
flooded	O
Raphael	I-PER
Likud	I-ORG
Benetton	I-ORG
Pohang	I-ORG
nabs	O
Named	O
Fabrizio	I-PER
Manne	I-PER
1915.00	O
Names	I-MISC	I-ORG
Ballanger	I-PER
62nd	O
looted	O
Karl	I-PER
473-6	O
Brigita	I-PER
Bohinen	I-PER
Brandi	I-PER
blizzard	O
parents	O
Peiris	I-PER
semi-upright	O
Marina	I-PER
Marine	I-ORG
cordon	O
emergency	O
Oh	O
Of	O
couple	O
486.5	O
Oy	I-ORG
Stoke	I-ORG
48.637	O
Op	O
ON	O
OM	I-ORG
Yulia	I-PER
spine	O
OF	I-MISC	I-LOC	O
OB	I-ORG
individuals	O
Stentex	I-ORG
OR	B-LOC
privately	O
reelection	O
methods	O
Brazilian	I-MISC
reperforated	O
bounce	O
directorate-grade	O
Eyewitnesses	O
VICTORY	O
oil-rich	O
Frank	I-PER
novelty	O
52-week	O
behave	O
Franz	I-PER
Aviation	I-MISC	I-ORG
20-minute	O
KABUL	I-LOC
concealed	O
Kamoga	I-PER
Paralympic	I-MISC
CAMAT	I-ORG
deserves	O
Bunce	I-PER
Rican	I-MISC	I-ORG
FRIENDLY	O
terrorists	O
into	O
Shay	I-PER
legalise	O
Shah	I-PER
span	O
gases	O
pinch-hits	O
Fleuchaus	I-PER
opens	O
6-98	O
considerably	O
considerable	O
intestines	O
Mutola	I-PER
Consolidated	I-ORG
maturity	O
faded	O
camp	O
Apex	I-ORG
influence	O
Schmidbauer	I-PER
diverse	O
Twins	I-ORG
chat	O
Sierra	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
A-rated	O
Phillies	I-ORG
uranium	O
Gephardt	I-PER
5-all	O
Mirren	I-ORG
Gurion	I-LOC
rubella	O
oblige	O
reinsurance	O
tendinitis	O
Impala	I-ORG
lane	O
land	O
liaising	O
Wataru	I-PER
Devers	I-PER
Leipzig	I-LOC
purged	O
beverage	O
Jim	I-PER
Ljupce	I-LOC
broader	O
Biogen	I-ORG
humpback	O
detectives	O
rejoined	O
resources	O
deficit	O
K.T.	I-PER
boatload	O
Nobilo	I-PER
minerals	O
PREMIUM	O
fewer	O
world-class	O
Rastegar	I-PER
590	O
593	O
597	O
599	O
598	O
video	O
Zickler	I-PER
dynamics	O
Etruscan	I-MISC
Bhavan	I-ORG
Legia	I-ORG
turnaround	O
flowing	O
harassing	O
2,036	O
Brasilia	I-LOC
90-day	O
Tillekeratne	I-PER
DISAPPOINTING	O
survey	O
makes	O
maker	O
Category	O
Santapaola	I-PER
7.50	O
7.56	O
confidence	O
Presently	O
2,017.99	O
next	O
EMBASSY	I-MISC
NATO	I-ORG
Mhow	I-LOC
Croatia-Yugoslavia	I-LOC
Suspected	O
BOND	O
rich	O
41.8	O
41.5	O
interogation	O
41.0	O
baby	O
central	I-ORG	O
Republican-led	I-MISC
customer	O
18,174,000	O
6-0-47-0	O
Fiedler	I-PER
40,144	O
wedge	O
process	O
lock	O
rode	O
promotional	O
Droits	I-ORG
Siraj	I-PER
educational	O
Eldred	O	I-PER
procured	O
comedy	O
Friends	I-ORG
7-15	O
denounce	O
STOCKS	O
GDANSK	I-LOC
varied	O
Results	O
One	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
Oct.	O
thigh	O
insight	O
directs	O
perfect	O
Trenidad	I-PER
MEHRTENS	I-PER
equalise	O
Brooks	I-ORG	I-PER
Cabinet	I-ORG	O
meantime	O
Championships	I-MISC
stalled	O
Brooke	I-PER
hijackers	O
teetotaller	O
5-55	O
5-56	O
Raoux	I-PER
Worku	I-PER
STOCK	O
Neiland	I-PER
Emmanuel	I-PER
shortage	O
Vavuniya	I-LOC
bump	O
Nadon	I-PER
FOUR	O
books	O
Deon	I-PER
Carbondale	I-ORG
fundamentally	O
'	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
rigging	O
incompetence	O
Shortly	O
Henman	I-PER
DISMISSES	O
chilli	O
Angola	I-LOC
could	O
Juliana	I-PER
Tatarstan	I-LOC
repeats	O
Riel	I-LOC	I-PER
Ried	I-ORG
scene	O
1347	O
starker	O
WORKS	O
Iran	I-LOC	I-ORG
Eastern	I-MISC	I-ORG
ordering	O
Botafogo	I-ORG
BUNOL	I-LOC
Iraq	I-LOC
interests	O
enforcement	O
stomach	O
ragbag	O
millfeeds	O
Roosevelt	I-LOC	I-PER
Excise	O
LANDSKRONA	I-LOC
Piskula	I-PER
+18.3	O
110.4	O
false	O
shrinks	O
27.22	O
27.25	O
tonight	O
4064/89	O
ponders	O
mountainous	O
Podkopayeva	I-PER
FIFTH	O
worldwide	O
Pierce	I-PER
Nieland	I-PER
2,555.16	O
Reserve	I-ORG	O
so-called	O
Montpellier	I-ORG
bred	O
lots	O
METROSTAV	I-ORG
Tender	I-LOC
Lezama	I-PER
Brandes	I-PER
3-mth	O
nominally	O
quickened	O
TENNIS	O
First-place	O
Walton	I-PER
bombings	O
riding	O
preliminaries	O
Dutroux	I-PER
changeup	O
Kryvy	I-ORG
Rating	I-ORG	O
taxes	O
`SERIOUS	O
Brent	I-MISC	I-ORG
guessing	O
downward	O
frame	O
Beograd	I-ORG
Pa	I-LOC
LISTING	O
Petrobulk	I-ORG
Po	I-PER
LUSAKA	I-LOC
Tempelhof	I-LOC
PP	I-ORG
Haldtime	O
PT	I-ORG
nuclear	O
Aloys	I-PER
Hollioake	I-PER
PC	I-ORG
PA	I-ORG
PF	I-ORG
PO	I-ORG
PM	O
SKHIRAT	I-LOC
Surinamese	I-MISC
P.	I-PER
GLASGOW	I-LOC
Sloga	I-ORG
Sorrento	I-PER
assisted-suicide	O
conclude	O
near-term	O
McPaul	I-PER
Meadows	I-LOC
Huracan-Corrientes	I-ORG
homocide	O
Aziz	I-PER
feather	O
commuter	O
4,175	O
commuted	O
Yone	I-PER
81.58	O
Violeta	I-PER
Battle	I-MISC	I-ORG
fielding	O
midweek	O
Piper	I-ORG
Fuel	O
ransom	O
denial	O
newsroom	O
280,556	O
Monica	I-PER
14,390.7	O
production-sharing	O
unsympathetic	O
Decker	I-PER
Ravindra	I-PER
identity	O
off	O
shotgun	O
Hashan	I-PER
Colombo	I-LOC	I-PER
administered	O
Rangarajan	I-PER
Besiktas	I-ORG
1.20	O
1.26	O
1.24	O
newest	O
Huddart	I-PER
Sutjeska	I-ORG
Zhanna	I-PER
wet	O
Gcaleka	I-PER
villagers	O
biologists	O
Patten	I-PER
Pirates	I-ORG	I-PER
bulge	O
Eelam	I-ORG
318-2	O
Agents	O
become	O
Chryste	I-PER
FIRM	O
underwent	O
choosing	O
recognition	O
passion	O
Moya	I-PER
Boudova	I-PER
pressure	O
half-time	O
infiltrating	O
lifestyle	O
debentures	O
Mestiri	I-PER
documentary	O
swimming	O
letters	O
pro-baseball	O
Greenville	I-ORG
VENTURA	I-LOC
terminated	O
reactivate	O
Crooks	I-PER
terminates	O
Billings	I-LOC
bagged	O
Contract	O
Okuda	I-PER
84.5	O
tossed	O
places	O
placed	O
problem	O
Nagyatad	I-LOC
quarries	O
Berkshire	I-ORG
nurses	O
disengagement	O
compared	O
nonetheless	O
deadly	O
Vinod	I-PER
Mehemdagic	I-PER
compares	O
details	O
Corp.	I-ORG
worthwile	O
illusion	O
ponytail	O
rebelled	O
February	O
repeat	O
lauds	O
Juppe	I-PER
U	I-PER
repeal	O
Backley	I-PER
exposure	O
searches	O
Breukink	I-PER
Corps	I-ORG
Nonferrous	I-ORG
compete	O
searched	O
tax-exempt	O
Qidra	I-PER
Roche	I-PER
4-35	O
4-36	O
4-31	O
2,200	O
Immediate	O
Lanner	I-PER
worth	O
union-based	O
Shaughnessy	I-PER
Military	I-ORG
2.7975	O
Anne-Gaelle	I-PER
exaggerate	O
post-closing	O
samurai	O
Zhichao	I-PER
cms	O
ATLANTIC	I-LOC
machines	O
Gama	I-ORG
Sally	I-PER
tie-up	O
Marwan	I-PER
PARIS	I-LOC
richest	O
protection	O
ploughed	O
obtained	O
postpones	O
stressed	O
Kroslak	I-PER
postponed	O
Absolute	O
276-277	O
Dfl	I-MISC
plot	O
Kamuzu	I-PER
abusing	O
110th	O
regrouping	O
championships	O
allies	O
blocking	O
1991	O
1990	I-MISC	O
1993	O
1992	I-MISC	O
1995	O
1994	O
divorced	O
1996	I-MISC	O
1999	O
1998	O
lb-3	O
lb-2	O
lb-5	O
lb-4	O
divorces	O
era	O
elbow	O
Steels	I-PER
Batting	O
Montenegrin	I-MISC
indicated	O
flung	O
indicates	O
Abu	I-LOC	I-PER
recovery	O
carriers	O
inhabitants	O
recovers	O
Jonty	I-PER
Allahu	I-PER
resignation	O
LATEST	O
customs	O
Duluth	I-LOC
8-6	O
elusive	O
Wickman	I-PER
appreciate	O
Ternopil	I-ORG
CALL	O
non-prescription	O
Fannie	I-PER
12.3	O
12.2	O
12.0	O
12.5	O
oilfield	O
12.9	O
Fujiwara	I-PER
Drew	I-PER
production	O
understated	O
Banda	I-PER
skills-based	O
coffee	O
Oman	I-LOC
safe	O
Omar	I-PER
Studentesc	I-ORG
strategic	O
Saunders	I-MISC
routines	O
l	I-MISC
Archaeological	I-ORG
reasonable	O
dumping	O
two-tiered	O
Alekna	I-PER
1,574,799	O
Clerq	I-PER
recomposed	O
disputed	O
Salzburg	I-ORG
disputes	O
detecting	O
baseman	O
refugee	O
renew	O
U.K.	I-LOC
immolation	O
hamstring	O
EUROLIRA	I-ORG
another	O
Manfred	I-PER
electronic	O
SEOUL	I-LOC
approximately	O
Arjuna	I-PER
dogs	O
3.13	O
Rare	O
Andersson	I-PER
Swerford	I-LOC
guilt	O
historical	O
Q1	O
Q3	O
Q2	O
Q4	I-ORG	O
Norbu	I-PER
Talbott	I-PER
Gavin	I-PER
contents	O
praising	O
convenient	O
Ericks	I-PER
Pierre-Henri	I-PER
unsecured	O
culminated	O
nobody	O
Costain	I-ORG
germany	I-LOC
Luca	I-PER
assessed	O
Mironivka	I-ORG
reserve	O
PAP	I-ORG
PAY	O
PAO	I-ORG
Santiago	I-LOC	I-PER
Lisheen	I-LOC
Englishmen	I-MISC
marketings	O
Nantes	I-ORG
beheads	O
COLORADO	I-ORG
Llansantffraid	I-ORG
haunted	O
Sask	I-LOC
runs	O
Agent	I-MISC
38.11	O
insurgents	O
secretary	O
Alexei	I-PER
Jackson	I-PER
Caracas	I-LOC
AEX	I-MISC
chief-of-staff	O
discussions	O
AEK	I-ORG
Malawi	I-LOC
techniques	O
draws	O
away	O
cooperation	O
drawn	O
superstores	O
MEES	I-MISC
Domingo	I-PER
handful	O
Padraig	I-PER
climate	O
volcano-hit	O
Erdei	I-PER
Dawn	I-PER
disappears	O
MOF	I-ORG
99.956	O
tone	O
Neagle	I-PER
tons	O
Ireland	I-LOC	I-ORG
telecommunications	O
gratitude	O
Kerry	I-PER
.359	O
.356	O
.357	O
.354	O
.353	O
102-0	O
attacked	O
Elections	I-ORG	O
attacker	O
GENOA	I-LOC	I-ORG
Broward	I-ORG
Kundic	I-PER
35th	O
DHAKA	I-LOC
Athens	I-LOC	I-ORG
separatist	O
tissue	O
conf	O
Convention	I-MISC	I-ORG
CVG	I-ORG
Thirty-six	O
wheel	O
hang	O
counterparts	O
hand	O
liberties	O
fuse	O
Salvation	I-ORG
camping	O
al-Turabi	I-PER
1600	O
humble	O
1605	O
Parma	I-ORG
client	O
Portland	I-LOC
Duff	I-ORG
Werder	I-ORG
Cambodia	I-LOC
Werdel	I-PER
Lorenzo	I-ORG	I-PER
thanks	O
volumetric	O
tramples	O
Al-Aqsa	I-LOC
concerns	O
Eighth	O
Rica-Nicaragua	I-LOC
Stahl	I-ORG
Lancer	I-MISC
Lancet	I-ORG
112.0-149.0	O
tendered	O
cooler	O
night	O
Maribor	I-LOC
Sadiki	I-PER
Ewe	I-PER
Inez	I-PER
Commission	I-MISC	I-ORG
Unitaire	I-ORG
Ines	I-PER
bore	O
confusing	O
LeBoeuf	I-PER
asking	O
Trnava	I-ORG
Riedle	I-PER
participation	O
Graz	I-ORG
Lopetegui	I-PER
Steven	I-PER
Neal	I-PER
Near	I-MISC	I-LOC
Carneiro	I-PER
Graf	I-PER
24/08	O
7546	O
Puglisi	I-PER
Abdullah	I-PER
profession	O
attorney	O
GAME	O
Caja	I-ORG
SOSA	I-PER
21.5	O
21.4	O
conservation	O
wrongdoing	O
ideologists	O
ceded	O
Iacomella	I-PER
low-lying	O
0645	O
maximum	O
Begum	I-PER
prayed	O
229-1	O
request	O
expertise	O
prayer	O
Norton	I-PER
x-PAO	I-ORG
McNamara	I-PER
Falls	I-LOC
test	O
immune-system	O
o'clock	O
update	O
BRAWL	O
Peacekeepers	O
ATAGI	I-LOC
Chanda	I-PER
Keller	I-PER
concept	O
diplomacy	O
Mathias	I-PER
redeployment	O
horseback	O
Republic	I-MISC	I-LOC
battle	O
soothed	O
Gornji	I-LOC
drunkards	O
Bury	I-ORG
Princes	I-LOC
10-year	O
hyper-inflationary	O
320.00	O
turns	O
gun	O
evades	O
guy	O
Petroecuador	I-ORG
goalscorers	O
Tavarez	I-PER
Jeter	I-PER
CME	I-ORG
Watts	I-ORG	I-PER
cost	O
Chisinau	I-ORG
rapist	O
HARLEYSVILLE	I-LOC
shares	O
Ford	I-MISC	I-ORG
shared	O
Fort	I-LOC
U.S.-bound	O
English	I-MISC
grabbed	O
Seneferu	I-PER
teacher	O
43.	O
sending	O
Portugal	I-LOC
spontaneous	O
Orphan	I-MISC
OKD	I-ORG
439	O
434	O
435	O
airbase	O
430	O
431	O
extra	O
Richterova	I-PER
uphill	O
3-116	O
WINNERS	I-MISC	O
Isaac	I-PER
Mediaset	I-ORG
firearm	O
softs	O
Dier	I-PER
STAYED	O
want-ad	O
rainfall	O
Kindercare	O
1676/96	I-MISC
pushed	O
8,600	O
totalled	O
Throughout	O
mild-mannered	O
ERP	I-ORG
Ernie	I-PER
chip	O
ERA	I-MISC
Pizzi	I-PER
occur	O
6-10	O
6-11	O
6-13	O
6-15	O
discussion	O
Furuya	I-PER
lounge	O
47-year-old	O
Rebel	O
Symcox	I-PER
3-33	O
deteriorate	O
product	O
APARTHEID	O
produce	O
Internazionale	I-ORG
Martin	I-PER
Dieter	I-PER
grandson	O
Radio	I-ORG	O
25TH	O
Rogachev	I-PER
Sheep	O
IPMA	O
approx	O
serving	O
Sheet	O
Jay	I-PER
Use	O
Jan	I-PER	O
ended	O
tablets	O
Ro	I-PER
50,000-seat	O
Mandela	I-PER
RE	O
2151	O
2158	O
Grabowksi	I-PER
emigrants	O
Faber	I-PER
introduce	O
55,000	O
BAYERISCHE	I-ORG
five-year-old	O
not	O
R.	I-PER
now	O
nor	O
Stakes	I-MISC
susceptibility	O
placate	O
drop	O
beings	O
Glenview	I-LOC
Agricultural	I-ORG
unloaded	O
Fes	I-ORG
policed	O
challenged	O
Endurance	I-MISC
Legal	I-ORG	O
challenges	O
hospice	O
replay	O
year	O
Expected	O
naming	O
monitors	O
61.45	O
bullish	O
Constanta	I-ORG
Norwegian	I-MISC
Vass	I-PER
355,900	O
unwanted	O
Segers	I-PER
transition	O
Erik	I-PER
invitation	O
512	O
Eric	I-PER
blind	O
Sprague	I-LOC
Stainless	I-MISC
758.75	O
Medicine	I-LOC
ring	O
tomorrow	O
Bruckner	I-PER
108.9	O
Lieutenant	O
Guimaraes	I-ORG
brains	O
disarmament-China	I-MISC
Jail	O
Refining	I-ORG
Kanstinger	I-PER
interbank	O
professionals	O
Bichette	I-PER
transferred	O
Acatepec	I-LOC
overhang	O
Burundi-Central	I-MISC
INNINGS	O
Marcos	I-MISC	I-PER
APPROVES	O
Libanais	I-ORG
CALIFORNIA	I-ORG
0400	O
Delegates	O
equipment	O
Unconfirmed	O
Unlike	O
COUPON	O
Gimnasia-Jujuy	I-ORG
reform	O
steady	O
AHOLD	I-ORG
3.72	O
3.73	O
3.70	O
3.75	O
scoreboard	O
discovered	O
snack	O
106.5	O
Zealander	I-MISC
580,000	O
7-0-35-0	O
TOWN	I-LOC
195.79	O
ex-world	O
Hijacked	O
burst	O
SPONSORS	O
EMU	I-MISC
actively	O
suspects	O
Kostadinova	I-PER
January-June	O
colours	O
Members	O
11,424.64	O
Isel	I-PER
na=not	O
hurts	O
WINS	O
Malaysia	I-LOC
downtrodden	O
AOL	I-ORG
madness	O
attache	O
Sachs	I-ORG
12.225	O
perpetrators	O
INEM	O
Meteorological	I-ORG
dictator	O
Doctors	O
Enderle	I-PER
PENH	I-LOC
fours	O
Telekom	I-ORG
suspected	O
Vincent	I-PER
Moody	I-ORG
Ravenna	I-ORG
metric	O
263-7	O
RUBIN	I-PER
waterway	O
Baulch	I-PER
Israel	I-LOC	I-ORG	B-LOC
develop	O
ONE-DAY	O
Azul	I-ORG
inquiry	O
Oyvind	I-PER
meteorological	O
SDV	I-ORG
Peruvian	I-MISC
Terence	I-PER
congressmen	O
Municipals	I-ORG
taxi	O
livestock	O
Service	I-ORG	O
foot	O
maternity	O
greetings	O
Vidal-Quadras	I-PER
death	O
Solano	I-PER
Spot	I-PER	O
1,400	O
halftime	O
overbought	O
Analyst	O
swim	O
amd	O
0.59	O
ramshackle	O
Imran	I-PER
using	O
0.53	O
0.55	O
fortune	O
annually	O
Gaidano	I-PER
fully	O
output	O
166-1	O
exposed	O
cathode	O
intend	O
Forsbrand	I-PER
Baltika	I-ORG
Symantec	I-ORG
three-engine	O
Earlier	O
Ion	I-PER
43-man	O
Minerals	I-ORG
Chilean	I-MISC
assembly	O
sixth	O
Premiership	O
fractured	O
assemble	O
2:29.34	O
exciting	O
Leonardo	I-PER
Almeida	I-PER
ideology	O
43-year	O
Chevron	I-ORG
97.42	O
Centers	I-ORG
freeing	O
Kapoor	I-PER
33.0	O
33.2	O
stabilisation	O
intervention	O
456.8	O
qualifying	O
start	O
stars	O
304,850	O
Azad	I-LOC
Sabag	I-PER
smuggling	O
pitcher	O
pitches	O
Mechelen	I-ORG
two-thirds	O
pitched	O
Mollenbeck	I-PER
fraud	O
Varteks	I-ORG
drachmas	O
Mozambican	I-MISC
600	O
603	O
Ferdinand	I-PER
Saarbruecken	I-LOC
Chua	I-PER
sixth-seeded	O
instantly	O
forcing	O
poor	O
ineligible	O
bacillus	O
March-May	O
drive-through	O
registry	O
25.49,(3-yr	O
38.43	O
pool	O
finished	O
firebreathing	O
karbovanets	O
60M	O
overseas	O
6,425	O
Unknown	O
48-year-old	O
month	O
unrest	O
unguent	O
religious	O
osteoporosis	O
corps	O
pledged	O
Uniceramic	I-ORG
Lubiani	I-PER
Phylis	I-PER
Hancock	I-PER
coloured	O
decide	O
Canard	I-ORG
locomotive	O
streets	O
3024.95	O
Mobbs	I-PER
General	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
Quepos	I-LOC
Korea	I-LOC
Patient	O
investing	O
Paribas	I-ORG
learned	O
THREAT	O
Chandrika	I-PER
tracks	O
bribes	O
excess	O
Nahar	I-LOC
conviction	O
inspired	O
losses	O
Dole	I-ORG	I-PER
heroin	O
advertising	O
Joao	I-PER
Sadova	I-PER
303.19	O
KIRKCALDY	I-LOC
requiring	O
put	O
S.	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-PER
A.S.	I-ORG
S$	I-MISC
conventional	O
Turkyilmaz	I-PER
WEATHER	O
lowering	O
fast-food	O
St	I-LOC	I-ORG
Banking	I-ORG	O
So	O
7000	O
Sa	I-PER
producing	O
grill	O
PUTS	O
SR	O
SP	O
SV	I-ORG
ST	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
SK	I-ORG
CEDAR	I-ORG
SC	I-ORG
SA	I-ORG
SG	I-ORG
740	O
F40	I-MISC
745	O
748	O
20-month-old	O
publicist	O
88-year-old	O
quartets	O
Innocent	I-PER
phrase	O
WEEKS	O
nine-month	O
375.00	O
third-placed	O
unlucky	O
Birch	I-PER
surpasses	O
vigilance	O
Television	I-ORG
BREAKS	O
scouts	O
Emirates	I-LOC
spate	O
Viacom	I-MISC	I-ORG
compulsory	O
Mexico	I-LOC	I-ORG
)	I-LOC	I-ORG	O	I-PER
Marathon	O
thermal	O
Atlas	I-ORG
Confederacy	I-ORG
wishful	O
absence	O
systems	O
slammed	O
Chong	I-ORG
Tarnovo	I-LOC
Lufthanseat	I-ORG
evening	O
Bournemouth	I-ORG
450,000	O
bless	O
sixth-inning	O
Liam	I-PER
heavy	O
Afghans	I-MISC
KSE	I-ORG
.446	O
.447	O
.444	O
.443	O
Farina	I-PER
testify	O
safety	O
7	O
MUZAFFARABAD	I-LOC
Town	I-LOC
None	O
earns	O
houses	O
hapless	O
Boston	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
Emajuddin	I-PER
Penrith	I-ORG
FERRIGATO	I-PER
Hawksworth	I-PER
07.00	O
Bharat	I-MISC
pro-opposition	O
horse	O
station	O
hundred	O
trapped	O
Yastrzhembsky	I-PER
1918	O
5,658	O
Palladini	I-PER
1913	O
1912	O
grew	O
state-owned	O
d'Italia	I-MISC
Senate	I-ORG
breadbasket	O
toward	O
Cecil	I-PER
881	O
884	O
BARRY	I-LOC
Poulenc	I-ORG
Peng	I-PER
Sellberg	I-PER
Pena	I-PER
Penn	I-ORG
Penh	I-LOC
adrift	O
Price	I-MISC	O	I-PER
Turnhout	I-LOC
2:30.67	O
left-field	O
Chief	O
hired	O
Hamiti	I-PER
Schweitzer	I-PER
Total	I-ORG	O
Hassane	I-PER
tubes	O
Masood	I-PER
phenomenon	O
hovered	O
1260	O
Johannesburg	I-LOC
stalker	O
Redmond	I-PER
justice	O
Buenaventura	I-LOC
French	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
Vaclavas	I-PER
CAC-40	I-MISC
criticising	O
Michelle	I-PER
feels	O
Grech	I-PER
competing	O
celebrates	O
retaliation	O
Novgorod	I-ORG
stored	O
after-hours	O
hype	O
Delmas	I-ORG
Franco	I-PER
12,300	O
France	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
45-50	O
mantra	O
Gibbs	I-PER
close	O
Roest	I-PER
locals	O
pictures	O
Officials	O
Brass	I-ORG
missing	O
158.82	O
ranked	O
abruptly	O
league	O
collaborators	O
Consultations	O
77-minute	O
minorities	O
Steve	I-PER
vault	O
experimental	O
Mr	O	I-PER
Haneda	I-LOC
CABINET	O
1997-98	O
threaten	O
Bogdan	I-PER
empty	O
Gingrich	I-ORG	I-PER
test-tube	O
lived	O
modelling	O
N	I-ORG	O
Donne	I-PER
Broadcasting	I-ORG
lives	O
Donna	I-PER
Heiko	I-PER
Hassan	I-PER
pact	O
dusty	O
ought	O
Asmara	I-LOC
riverways	O
guide	O
pack	O
costly	O
Thierry	I-PER
Slask	I-ORG
2,340.6	O
grant	O
Luke	I-PER
Luka	I-LOC
Oilseed	O
grand	O
Mauritania	I-LOC
abnormals	O
ratings	O
youngsters	O
003	O
000	O
vitriol	O
Akira	I-PER
consistency	O
mobs	O
settlements	O
technicians	O
Tyler	I-PER
possessors	O
questioned	O
Berkeley	I-PER
99.32	O
showing	O
.307	O
369.66	O
dearly	O
Maakinen	I-PER
popular	O
book-building	O
sketch	O
economic	O
Wembley	I-LOC
seven-newspaper	O
competitions	O
AMR	I-ORG
AMT	O
Protestant	O
Bild	I-ORG
Bill	I-MISC	I-PER
opposes	O
2/9	O
Etruria	I-LOC
2/3	O
8,333	O
Taylor	I-ORG	I-PER
silence	O
Stark	I-PER
mills	O
Boulder	I-LOC
Norman	I-PER
placing	O
visas	O
Kock	I-PER
Howe	I-PER
injection	O
Tosco	I-ORG
similar	O
ordered	O
Aviv	I-LOC	I-ORG
To	O
Edward	I-PER
2.00-2.25	O
Ta	I-PER
ancestors	O
TV	I-ORG	O
dashed	O
fears	O
TO	O
Claverie	I-PER
department	O
TE	I-ORG
absentia	O
CHILPANCINGO	I-LOC
T.	I-PER
T$	I-MISC
shrub	O
Uzi	I-MISC
resolving	O
837/763	O
bribe	O
Dostum	I-PER
Apparently	O
alien-led	O
Interpol	I-ORG
Bengal	I-LOC
FALL	O
Parent	O
Not	O
Nov	O
Now	O
friendly	O
Nor	O
Penrose	I-PER
acreage	O
telling	I-MISC	O
positions	O
21,718	O
8.90	O
56,126	O
No1	O
No2	O
Index	I-MISC	O
12-1-41-1	O
14,278.9	O
jump	O
199.71	O
Grid	O
64-stroke	O
Kristie	I-PER
3,920.7	O
Publisher	O
743.50	O
33,230	O
radicals	O
kidnapped	O
convert	O
Palace	I-LOC	I-ORG
Bach	I-PER
NYMEX	O
gene	O
Temperatures	O
Blake	I-PER
airspace	O
Doctor	O
manage	O
Friedick	I-PER
Contributing	O
4.75	O
LDP-dominated	I-MISC
11,244	O
Lecce	I-ORG
Bragantino	I-ORG
camera	O
historically	O
compatriot	O
Tunbridge	I-LOC
formally	O
BBB+	O
Boshova	I-PER
Markus	I-PER
joint-commission	O
CONSECUTIVE	O
appointed	O
meek	O
averaged	O
4:17.551	O
Birmingham	I-LOC	I-ORG
servants	O
meet	O
averages	O
withdrew	O
Israeli	I-MISC
links	O
Lovell	I-PER
Mr.	O
pulling	O
sought	O
Faldo	I-PER
Merchant	I-ORG
230	O
232	O
Alloa	I-ORG
0025	O
farm	O
outdid	O
thunderstorm	O
Mrs	O
Roman	I-MISC	B-MISC	I-PER
fouled	O
Alloy	O
Indore	I-LOC
famous	O
homered	O
Guard	I-ORG
favourites	O
Nicky	I-PER
including	O
DUTCH	I-MISC
RAF	I-ORG
2913/92	I-MISC
EASTERN	I-MISC
RAO	I-ORG
Rajapat	I-ORG
Gordana	I-PER
Sindh	I-ORG
kilometres	O
pre-war	O
CAIRO	I-LOC
university	O
Montpelier	I-LOC
Jonzon	I-PER
Specter	I-PER
prevailing	O
BOTHAM	I-PER
Statistics	I-ORG
supermodel	O
separating	O
special	O
Malgorzata	I-PER
entertainment	O
CEO	O
cause	O
undated	O
delegates	O
METRES	O
resumed	O
determining	O
times	O
mini-state	O
Sakai	I-LOC
fertiliser	O
powerful	O
MCMANAMAN	I-PER
Understating	O
Aryan	I-MISC
ankle	O
Dietmar	I-PER
KIRKLAND	I-LOC
LIMERICK	I-LOC
lists	O
Knaven	I-PER
chemicals	O
submitted	O
Zina	I-PER
Zinc	O
Oval	I-LOC
Akbar	O
enforced	O
EVEREN	I-ORG
horrors	O
Other	O
Warzycha	I-PER
Administrator	O
4:19.699	O
CUP	I-MISC
battles	O
relatives	O
battled	O
Pueblo	I-LOC
Puebla	I-ORG
subtracted	O
MATUZICI	I-LOC
astonishing	O
halting	O
Randy	I-PER
Abuja	I-LOC
SPLA	I-ORG
INTERVIEW-T&N	I-MISC
Lumir	I-PER
brighter	O
achieve	O
96.84	O
decentralisation	O
521-8	O
b-1	O
b-6	O
b-4	O
second-half	O
Iva	I-PER
JOCKEY	O
Forget	I-PER
tobacco	O
CANADIAN	I-MISC
Darlington	I-ORG
Paramaribo	I-LOC
Austrian	I-MISC
widow	O
Seng	I-MISC
immigrant	O
officials	O
reinforcements	O
operated	O
Gaudenzi	I-PER
Joulwan	I-PER
Wisconsin	I-LOC
nightmare	O
tyre	O
tens	O
Zvereva	I-PER
indiscriminate	O
key	O
2.40	O
hits	O
2.43	O
2.44	O
2.45	O
limits	O
strains	O
Loftus	I-LOC
90.85	O
Gillingham	I-ORG
diplomats	O
Amoco	I-ORG
Jaap	I-PER
thanked	O
cent	O
liberals	O
Mansfield	I-ORG
ECOMOG	I-ORG
shoulders	O
controlled	O
Steinbach	I-PER
Wellington	I-LOC
guerrillas	O
abortions	O
Consequently	O
Sturm	I-ORG
Hari	I-PER
05:53	O
26.7.1996	O
surface	O
examined	O
Traore	I-PER
INDIA	I-LOC
proceeds	O
Bangkok	I-LOC
KSE-100	I-MISC
parts	O
speaker	O
northwest	O
party	I-ORG	O
Aluminum	O
17-year-old	O
destruction	O
rift	O
Mentmore	I-ORG
Evelyn	I-PER
HELSINKI	I-LOC
dressed	O
warlord	O
Gordon	I-PER
Flower	I-PER
increasingly	O
Couto	I-PER
liked	O
43	O
AVIA	I-ORG
headed	O
O.K.	I-PER
Cheveley	I-ORG
balloons	O
Exposure	O
LUANDA	I-LOC
disappearance	O
EQUITY	O
Nelson	I-LOC	I-PER
HK$	I-MISC
loss	O
necessary	O
Aug.	O
lost	O
al-Risala	I-LOC
payments	O
Shrewsbury	I-ORG
lose	O
LAUDERDALE	I-LOC
trucked	O
library	O
French-registered	I-MISC
home	O
EEC	I-ORG
moderates	O
pinpoint	O
near-record	O
broad	O
objected	O
Newell	I-ORG
Enrico	I-PER
cradle	O
inflammation	O
Strang	I-PER
Bryant	I-PER
reaching	O
Official	O
Up	O
Quilter	I-PER
fifth-seeded	O
instability	O
Mental	O
UP	O
US	I-LOC	I-ORG
UN	I-ORG
Kassala	I-LOC
UK	I-LOC	I-ORG
Jordi	I-PER
13.26	O
tourists	O
previously	O
oportunity	O
cocoa	O
Internal	O
additional	O
lagged	O
Alomar	I-PER
Zagalo	I-PER
north	I-LOC	O
Moss	I-ORG
rioted	O
swastika-covered	O
blaming	O
Chamber	I-ORG
gain	O
sprinkling	O
highest	O
McGinley	I-PER
display	O
urging	O
marketplace	O
Iliescu	I-PER
Doorn	I-PER
beats	O
Wouden	I-PER
education	O
K.C.	I-PER
Leftist	O
Geneva	I-LOC
Neves	I-PER
Wells	I-LOC	I-PER
Delivery	O
Giles	I-PER
publicists	O
star	O
Jiangsu	I-LOC
stay	O
foil	O
stab	O
else	O
shunt	O
15-20	O
212-859-1610	O
Refined	O
Corsica	I-LOC
aided	O
Frontier	I-ORG
Annabel	I-PER
whoops	O
4:17.696	O
knelt	O
aides	O
consists	O
Honda	I-ORG
pensions	O
unionized	O
swap	O
Sheets	I-PER
Alkhan-Yurt	I-LOC
Kallis	I-PER
Megawati	I-PER
void	O
McKinnon	I-PER
.633	O
confederate	O
crops	O
unrelated	O
no.2	O
immunizes	O
enhance	O
whirlwind	O
breakouts	O
Christie	I-PER
likely	O
re-nominate	O
kidnap	O
Apertura	I-MISC
Arizona	I-LOC
spokesman	O
Kunar	I-LOC
foodstuffs	O
Baumann	I-PER
self-loading	O
men	O
Irwin	I-PER
met	O
Curry	I-PER
contraction	O
MATEO	I-LOC
Packaging	O
lucrative	O
Doncaster	I-MISC	I-ORG
uncompromising	O
fantastic	O
Russians	I-MISC
guests	O
Norske	I-ORG
Piano	O
Eveningperformance	I-PER
41.0-42.5	O
whatsoever	O
SUMMARY	O
Times-Stock	I-MISC
Betar	I-ORG
TriNations	I-MISC
room	O
FACILITIES	O
roof	O
movies	O
Fournier	I-PER
root	O
3,161	O
unmarked	O
+301	O
Corporation	I-ORG
stressing	O
Donkow	I-PER
10,000	O
foods	O
DAVIS	I-MISC
autonomy	O
first-inning	O
amazing	O
blanks	O
Lucas	I-PER
vicious	O
schoolchildren	O
Leicestershire	I-ORG
third	O
Ended	O
1578	O
684	O
operate	O
681	O
680	O
310.00	O
Haugland	I-PER
pothole	O
inconclusive	O
Mothusi	I-PER
Newark	I-LOC
soyoil	O
Bonetat	I-PER
before	O
10.0	O
10.3	O
10.5	O
18-man	O
10.6	O
10.9	O
10.8	O
388.55	O
388.50	O
crew	O
durum	O
Rishon	I-ORG
Pate	I-PER
stalemate	O
476/698	O
combination	O
Challenge	I-MISC
microfilm	O
Agenda	I-MISC
arrested	O
ventilation	O
Reggiana	I-ORG
wage	O
Rovers	I-ORG
03.684	O
skins	O
Tetouan	I-ORG
trading	O
merchants	O
.8787	O
SINGAPORE	I-LOC
Producers	I-ORG	O
Moin	I-PER
resume	O
ascending	O
Circuit	I-ORG
9-1-49-0	O
12.348	O
Munakarmi	I-PER
1,123	O
Adolf	I-PER
CANBERRA	I-LOC
107.55	O
floors	O
downside	O
bicycle	O
Ottey	I-PER
Underwriter	O
Hanson	I-ORG	I-PER
sex-and-murder	O
Matos	I-PER
Colorado	I-LOC	I-ORG
Yevgeny	I-PER
Charleston	I-LOC
Wroclaw	I-LOC	I-ORG
Rottweiler	I-MISC
bitterness	O
jeopardise	O
palace	O
AFRICAN	I-MISC	O
reassert	O
x-Cercle	I-ORG
OPTIONS	O
TEMPORARY	O
Egyptian	I-MISC
Csepel	I-ORG
TOSHIBA	I-MISC
fitting	O
worsening	O
Rodica	I-PER
01.77	O
Ivar	I-PER
Two-try	O
Ivan	I-PER
two-lane	O
observation	O
impostor	O
breathes	O
competitors	O
Nazism	I-MISC
coup	O
Gujar	I-LOC
probe	O
implying	O
Boeta	I-PER
21.25	O
Monstrose	I-ORG
northeast	O
weekends	O
jailer	O
Goran	I-PER
Others	O
jailed	O
Havana	I-LOC
endorse	O
12,700-12,800	O
watermelon	O
earn	O
Hendrika	I-PER
troop	O
Hendriks	I-PER
ears	O
Partners	I-ORG
folly	O
diminutive	O
Perfetti	I-PER
testing	O
Veerle	I-PER
Somebody	O
artificial	O
44th	O
physicist	O
Georgios	I-PER
suggested	O
civilised	O
resistant	O
uncertainty	O
Naoto	I-PER
Amina	I-PER
Bahamas	I-LOC
foray	O
drilled	O
Inchon	I-LOC
putt	O
puts	O
basis	O
patrolling	O
tiny	O
commission	O
interest	O
basic	O
Marxist-Leninist	I-ORG
entered	O
lovely	I-MISC
BRITISH	I-MISC
shattering	O
Comisetti	I-PER
Stuart	I-PER
Voica	I-PER
unpopular	O
spontaneously	O
ugly	O
APPEAL	O
8,757	O
pessimistic	O
seven	O
cane	O
V.	I-PER
colonies	O
Zilina	I-ORG
meets	O
bearded	O
undaunted	O
VS	O
VW	I-MISC	I-ORG
Usually	O
Va	I-LOC
programs	O
failing	O
Estudiantes	I-ORG
800	O
investments	O
805	O
804	O
Gillian	I-PER
Pinsent	I-PER
yen	O
fighters	O
year-old	O
yes	O
yet	O
nudge	O
royal	O
FIGHTBACK	O
contestant	O
save	O
Sidot	I-PER
Sidor	I-ORG
REFUNDING	O
nationalists	O
Overseas	I-ORG	O
Art	I-PER
Michele	I-PER
Are	O
20-man	O
deal	O
bookseller	O
deaf	O
dead	O
shuttled	O
Siegl	I-PER
RALLYING	O
carts	O
Hernan	I-PER
1998/99	O
1:53.067	O
predicting	O
translated	O
Corey	I-PER
CRAWLEY	I-PER
confrontation	O
end-of-season	O
384.00	O
Tokyo-Mitsubishi	I-ORG
SNCF	I-ORG
magazine	I-ORG	O
Gremio	I-ORG
Including	O
afternoon	O
automatically	O
managers	O
Seychellois	I-MISC
refiner	O
SACK	O
down	O
Chairmen	O
refined	O
Kwazulu-Natal	I-LOC
murderers	O
communists	O
Unless	O
113.0	O
initial	O
NBH	I-ORG
editor	O
fraction	O
NBC	I-ORG
NBA	I-ORG
factions	O
Herman	I-PER
Rahul	I-PER
some	O
landing	O
34-20	O
analyst	O
Noce	I-PER
Franka	I-PER
H.K.	I-LOC
assessment	O
Attempts	O
whisker	O
long-distance	O
strengthening	O
Dreekman	I-PER
Nuclear	O
one-third	O
tarnished	O
Battersby	I-PER
Indusind	I-ORG
Tiber	I-ORG
Tibet	I-LOC
Persons	I-ORG
faction	O
Granic	I-PER
journey	O
Fluminense	I-ORG
Cathy	I-PER
weekend	O
happening	O
stripping	O
restored	O
hijacker	O
Torino	I-ORG
Winning	O
Desmond	I-PER
hijacked	O
21st	I-MISC	O
Tremila	I-ORG
Nilis	I-PER
DALLAS	I-LOC
father	O
0	O
swoop	O
sovereignty	O
adviser	O
Valerenga	I-ORG
pro-child	O
defying	O
advised	O
Financial	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
proposals	O
Mahmoud	I-PER
round	O
talked	O
dealing	O
Sidwell	I-ORG
Darren	I-PER
Dnevi	I-ORG
Lago	I-PER
bombardment	O
hospitalised	O
Kahalani	I-PER
413.20	O
targets	O
majors	O
Head	I-PER
Chiapas	I-LOC
suspect	O
international	O
filled	O
Bishops	I-ORG
Bids	O
Wijaya	I-PER
1-48	O
DSE	I-ORG
Trafford	I-LOC
box	O
boy	O
Yongchaiyudh	I-PER
Session	O
diagnosed	O
teenage	O
merely	O
Beryllium	O
sweating	O
sake	O
visit	O
COMPETITIVE	O
AUG	O
freestyle	O
63,000	O
JOIN	O
Rebels	O
reelected	O
making	O
nearest	O
Avaz	I-ORG
14p	O
pointedly	O
8703080	O
9,500	O
Tristan	I-PER
overreacting	O
Coltart	I-PER
Sun-ho	I-MISC
146	O
147	O
144	O
145	O
142	O
143	O
140	O
16,909,000	O
148	O
149	O
membership	O
Sjoberg	I-PER
14.	O
waist	O
Series	I-MISC	O
Charleroi	I-LOC	I-ORG
Nicaraguan	I-MISC
shoes	O
setbacks	O
police	O
monitor	O
hat-trick	O
Rain	O
Regis	I-PER
3,850	O
3,853	O
policy	O
GATTING	I-PER
rattled	O
Kyle	I-PER
Elland	I-LOC
lunch	O
markings	O
fourth-stage	O
III	I-PER
Seville	I-LOC
2,020.82	O
IVAC	I-ORG
elephants	O
Holdings	I-ORG
14.12	O
treacherous	O
Ken	I-PER
Olympiakos	I-ORG
nominal	O
Aires	I-LOC	I-ORG
Key	O	I-PER
assurance	O
Commerce	I-ORG
G	O
Rights	I-ORG
4-334	O
Sometimes	O
Luigi	I-PER
Beauvau	I-LOC
carnival	O
waiter	O
Baku	I-LOC
Tirol	I-ORG
Huntington	I-LOC
11.959	O
waited	O
first	O
fleeing	O
Black	I-LOC	O	I-PER
zvezda	I-ORG
tiebreak	O
PVS	O
lambasts	O
Jalalabad	I-LOC
moisture	O
Karame	I-PER
speaking	O
adjourned	O
allegedly	O
Krylya	I-ORG
Midfielders	O
61st	O
Ashta	I-LOC
Escravos	I-ORG
20s	O
4-1/2	O
Rockies	I-ORG
Expectations	O
Tight	O
.520	O
.523	O
.522	O
.524	O
.527	O
.526	O
recreated	O
wild-card	O
Murphy	I-PER
shocked	O
squad	O
interior	I-ORG	O
109.45	O
Kazakhstan	I-LOC
600,000	O
ultimate	O
201	O
200	O
203	O
202	O
Rugby	I-ORG	O
204	O
207	O
206	O
209	O
DHA	I-ORG
SKOPJE	I-LOC
Gulbuddin	I-PER
sheets	O
complaints	O
upland	O
Keane	I-ORG	I-PER
20.	O
radioactive	O
172.7	O
143.60	O
WA	B-LOC
Barry	I-PER
representatives	O
WW	O
222,457	O
high-profile	O
Across	I-ORG
enthusiast	O
We	O
treasure	O
storms	O
RIO	I-LOC
RIF	I-ORG
enthusiasm	O
pegged	O
RIA	I-ORG
Zrubakova	I-PER
Zarcas	I-LOC
12.60	O
get	O
hailed	O
Alania	I-ORG
Right	O
seared	O
Angel	I-PER
W.	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
morning	O
undertone	O
Education	I-ORG	O
5.40	O
declared	O
Grant	I-PER
Provide	I-MISC
seat	O
Vital	I-ORG
declares	O
SPECTATOR	O
Grand	I-MISC	B-MISC	O
Kucan	I-PER
satisfying	O
Drummond	I-PER
enough	O
across	O
Goldiner	I-PER
infrastructure	O
FOR	O
CLUB	O
CONTRIBUTED	O
FOB	O
Each	O
nationality	O
coupons	O
staged	O
blasts	O
tour	O
Miljenko	I-PER
among	O
Class-A	O
Nikiforov	I-PER
Riley	I-PER
considering	O
Assembly	I-ORG
capable	O
NATO-led	I-MISC
18:00	O
Ludmila	I-PER
four-game	O
oust	O
squash	O
10th-ranked	O
dramatic	O
wake	O
metals	O
declaration	O
Action	I-ORG
Streda	I-ORG
sound	O
409	O
1100	O
promising	O
cancelled	O
investigating	O
408	O
falsified	O
Sudan	I-LOC	I-ORG
strait	O
sleeping	O
strain	O
sudden	O
protein	O
Danut	I-PER
Nele	I-PER
Footwork	O
compiling	O
Govt.Fcast	O
Gianluca	I-PER
extended	O
Bosnia	I-LOC
Monsignor	O
Barcelona	I-LOC	I-ORG
annulled	O
motorcade	O
Harding	I-PER
businesslike	O
Motors	I-ORG
Carlton	I-ORG
convened	O
outdoor	O
15-month	O
sights	O
94.00	O
unofficial	O
Shuzo	I-PER
A1	O
rental	O
forgo	O
Nisbet	I-PER
GAZA	I-LOC
30-year	O
Lambruschini	I-PER
GRAND	I-MISC	B-MISC	O
Ebe	I-PER
Ashia	I-PER
've	O
passionate	O
FSU	I-ORG
2778	O
MOSCOW	I-LOC
AC	I-ORG
Oremans	I-PER
Assurance	I-ORG
HOUSTON	I-ORG
outs	O
96.00	O
reportedly	O
drenched	O
stages	O
kms	O
knife	O
Muasher	I-PER
each	O
Vietnam	I-MISC
Hishem	I-PER
AP	I-ORG
DUBLIN	I-LOC
fertile	O
coupon	O
skilled	O
Zeleznik	I-ORG
Chatuparisut	I-PER
deadlines	O
Thomson	I-ORG	I-PER
post-Second	I-MISC
MIAMI	I-LOC
5.2420	O
arranged	O
year-olds	O
arranger	O
Angeles-based	I-MISC
powerless	O
Hershiser	I-PER
Satoshi	I-PER
Knobl	I-PER
censor	O
examine	O
Stubbs	I-PER
casualty	O
again	O
strikers	O
Sarka	I-PER
Ove	I-PER
earth-shattering	O
1249-1286	O
nine-to-one	O
487	O
islanders	O
483	O
482	O
assets	O
deja-voodoo	O
76-year-old	O
CHILE	I-LOC
lapped	O
founder	O
Workers	I-ORG	O
founded	O
TOGO	I-LOC
expressions	O
Jomhuri	I-ORG
shattered	O
Championship	I-MISC	O
+48	O
+49	O
+44	O
+45	O
+47	O
TAX	O
+41	O
preserved	O
enjoying	O
Ciller	I-PER
sitting	O
Sebastian	I-PER
20th	O
SWIMMING	O
clinch	O
Banglabazar	I-ORG
Andria	I-ORG
zero	O
perspective	O
226-5	O
AGGRESSIVE	O
226-1	O
defence	O
brackets	O
sides	O
caffeine	O
11.61	O
5000	O
malaria	O
managerless	O
6.72	O
squeezed	O
furlongs	O
^^^^^	Start
Gil	I-ORG
lasagna	O
Basuki	I-PER
misery	O
Reform	I-MISC	I-ORG
N'DJAMENA	I-LOC
GOOCH	I-PER
Dolly	I-MISC
shareholders	O
Pieter	I-PER
correspondents	O
Wally	I-PER
0.005	O
Zardari	I-PER
American	I-MISC	I-ORG
Roger	I-PER
24.25	O
Communist-led	I-MISC
hour	O
chardonnay	O
recall	O
Activists	O
sucks	O
Hamlet	I-MISC
guards	O
remain	O
stubborn	O
Sesa	I-PER
collision	O
minimum	O
Sese	I-PER
numbers	O
Calif	I-LOC
narrowly	O
needs	O
needy	O
technology	O
acts	O
sacred	O
civilisation	O
Schneider	I-PER
Tankan	I-ORG
questioning	O
fast-growing	O
4-ounce	O
coming	O
Kelly	I-PER
Muscular	O
skilful	O
ANCHORAGE	I-LOC
inventing	O
BRATISLAVA	I-LOC
Internacional	I-ORG
through	O
Forces	I-ORG
Xavier	I-PER
26:43.53	O
pct	O
seasonally	O
Elijah	I-PER
forints	O
Notts	I-ORG
7.03	O
Cukurova	I-ORG
Plavsic	I-PER
frigid	O
compound	O
Taipei	I-LOC	I-ORG
restrict	O
658/96	O
hails	O
evade	O
engaging	O
hive	O
Welspun	I-ORG
assigns	O
20-24C	O
Mohajir	I-ORG
Cook	I-PER
Chirchir	I-PER
Muster	I-PER
0100	O
extraordinary	O
LIONS	I-ORG
Rishon-Lezion	I-LOC
impeached	O
backed	O
reparations	O
beginning	O
Nielsen	I-PER
parred	O
Pantic	I-PER
Kurdish-controlled	I-MISC
2.26	O
Soir	I-ORG
Boldon	I-PER
XI	I-ORG	O
Justin	I-PER
a.s.	I-ORG
Sibonina	I-ORG
Partnership	I-MISC
Woodlands	I-LOC
confessional	O
Hammerson	I-ORG
5-67	O
showers	O
left-hander	O
5-68	O
Bernardo	I-PER
Power	I-ORG	I-PER
Ukrainian	I-MISC	I-ORG
+431	O
lifts	O
SOYBEAN	O
Tarak	I-PER
godfather	O
chart	O
services	O
three-pointer	O
dystrophy	O
McGilley	I-PER
curtain-raiser	O
+381	O
rebels	O
passer-by	O
businesses	O
Kathy	I-PER
cell	O
merger	O
Sellers	O
idiots	O
Hermawan	I-PER
chimed	O
1315	O
Nepali	I-MISC	I-ORG
cholera	O
express	O
Venantius	I-ORG
Serbian	I-MISC
motorcycles	O
Minneapolis	I-LOC
doubles	O
restaurants	O
64ths-inch	O
SKS	I-ORG
Citing	O
Cunningham	I-PER
reopening	O
Zylstra	I-PER
expert	O
+12,696	O
eight-year	O
Richards	I-PER
cutout	O
Richardt	I-PER
27.53	O
Detective	O
restaurant	O
Rusedski	I-PER
foreign	O
Green	I-PER
elaborating	O
point	O
gypsy	O
expensive	O
123rd-ranked	O
weaving	O
screened	O
rivals	O
four-run	O
16-year-old	O
six-party	O
Stockholm	I-LOC	I-ORG
Rory	I-PER
AGF-IART	I-ORG
politician	O
grains	O
elections	O
Dissident	O
PRE-SALE	O
century	O
12.434	O
confining	O
Zanini	I-PER
6mth	O
overflying	O
development	O
currencies	O
NATIONS	I-MISC	I-ORG
Kreissig	I-PER
1968	O
Provisional	I-ORG
Zionists	I-MISC
downtrend	O
task	O
PLANE	O
withdraw	O
year-on-year	O
Albans	I-LOC
shape	O
1963	O
Kenyan	I-MISC
timber	O
50-year-old	O
cut	O
cup	O
source	O
Christopher	I-LOC	I-PER
renominate	O
Commons	I-ORG
Exploration	O
Damion	I-PER
Takeda	I-PER
loyalist	O
foolish	O
machinegun	O
unhindered	O
Management	I-ORG	O
nc=acomparison	O
diocese	O
absolutely	O
2-5080815	O
delegation	O
prefessors	O
Lebouc	I-PER
Dakar	I-LOC
year-half	O
culprit	O
MEETING	O
decision	O
Togo	I-LOC
Boy	I-MISC
186th-ranked	O
strapped	O
paedophile	O
Harper-Collins	I-ORG
Voorhis	I-ORG
Radstrom	I-PER
Frenz	I-PER
Romania	I-LOC
slams	O
Twyford	I-LOC
Flamengo	I-ORG
Bayle	I-PER
Captain	O
medallist	O
retailer	O
Wash.-based	I-MISC
787.50	O
normality	O
1.50	O
1.56	O
1.55	O
1.59	O
Ruano-Pascual	I-PER
Haga	I-PER
Stephenson	I-PER
underlined	O
subsidiary	O
Wang	I-PER
Beijing	I-LOC
Bennett	I-PER
W.C.	I-LOC
planes	O
Lindy	I-PER
constant	O
consulted	O
curb	O
Babes	I-LOC
Linda	I-PER
Unitog	I-ORG
adoring	O
Israelis	I-MISC
ADDIS	I-LOC
Bowles	I-PER
107-12	O
107-10	O
modem-chip	O
intensified	O
restoration	O
cater	O
utterly	O
deterrence	O
bankers	O
Sahara	I-MISC
Editorial	I-ORG	O
PHILLIES	I-ORG
RABAT	I-LOC
wrangle	O
36,5	O
cannabis	O
welter	O
Gazprom	I-ORG
pleasing	O
nervousness	O
presently	O
unhurt	O
entire	O
announcing	O
Murat	I-PER
ceasefire	O
solutions	O
Howard	I-PER
rivers	O
Kleiner	I-ORG
assisted	O
access	O
21,000	O
Butte	I-MISC
PAKISTAN	I-LOC
29TH	O
pinch-hitter	O
24TH	O
7706	O
talent	O
Jennifer	I-PER
212-859-1710	O
principally	O
implement	O
Proceeds	O
Amtrak	I-ORG
Gente	I-ORG
bushman	O
Quarterfinals	O
composer	O
Aston	I-ORG
oilfields	O
Mallinckrodt	I-ORG
classically	O
totality	O
year-ago	O
Nasr	I-ORG
prized	O
snatching	O
Sanath	I-PER
Gavaldon	I-PER
2,250	O
548	O
unwinding	O
majority	O
Liberec	I-ORG
0800	O
20-7	O
20-6	O
closing	O
*Note	O
PLO-Israel	I-MISC
YR	O
1,940	O
Yi	I-PER
six-hitter	O
AugSep	O
holds	O
Warrington	I-ORG
NZ$	I-MISC
Yr	O
Daewoo	I-ORG
profile	O
annualised	O
highs	O
Pellumbi	I-PER
1,294.5	O
chasing	O
guilder	O
947	O
941	O
furious	O
subsequently	O
.496	O
Qualifiers	O
.492	O
cease-fire	O
Kris	I-PER
disarm	O
symbols	O
report	O
Herzliya	I-ORG
horns	O
12,600-12,750	O
finalising	O
Magnus	I-PER
accredited	O
Zemun	I-ORG
half-percentage	O
later	O
squabbling	O
Robin	I-PER
preschool	O
Jimy	I-PER
Dillard	I-PER
oversubscribed	O
Moroccan	I-MISC
Jimi	I-PER
Gary	I-PER
3,003	O
3,000	O
sexual	O
Drnovsek	I-PER
Alastair	I-PER
MILLNS	I-PER
MANAGER	O
China	I-LOC	I-ORG
barley	O
Yingkou	I-LOC
approached	O
X-rays	O
Outlook	O
backwards	O
yard	O
Madrid	I-LOC	I-ORG
hinting	O
yarn	O
allied	O
8-9	O
205.10	O
8-4	O
Sammy	I-PER
8-0	O
8-1	O
domiciled	O
reaches	O
lagging	O
reached	O
SPRINT	O
DiSarcina	I-PER
flag	O
scant	O
Stocks	O
scans	O
Double-A	O
explanation	O
acquire	O
200-an-hour	O
Gaines	I-PER
Freiburg	I-LOC	I-ORG
Bordeaux	I-LOC	I-ORG
Zoran	I-PER
Reds	I-ORG
bodyguard	O
Pound	O
224,609	O
have	O
throat	O
Bourlet	I-PER
incentive	O
tranches	O
whistle-stop	O
procure	O
prisoner	O
payment	O
inexorable	O
Vinnytsya	I-LOC	I-ORG
disease	O
1,000	I-MISC	O
1,002	O
1,003	O
Joyce	I-PER
occasion	O
Banco	I-ORG
recess	O
demurred	O
Hatoyama	I-PER
85-year-old	O
TENDER	O
Regan	I-PER
communism	O
knowledge	O
MATURITY	O
dystrophin	O
Jacob	I-PER
communist	O
regularly	O
hijacking	O
Finnish	I-MISC
142.3	O
Tanzania	I-LOC
700,000	O
Costantino	I-PER
teams	O
2060	O
fixed	O
2067	O
RETURN	O
Kornblum	I-PER
racked	O
showdown	O
LEAVE	O
racket	O
PAYING	O
attempting	O
36,000	O
difficulties	O
boundary	O
Concerto	O
REOFFER	O
sorrow	O
monarchy	O
Kashmir	I-LOC
Sobotzik	I-PER
revoked	O
joke	O
equal	O
OTTAWA	I-LOC
placebo	O
Morelia	I-ORG
Gras	I-PER
ambushed	O
disarmament	O
Bench	O	I-PER
swimmer	O
Thailand	I-LOC
EXCHANGE	O
Nations	I-MISC	I-ORG
tense	O
welcoming	O
Alleyne	I-PER
Maslova	I-PER
IT	O
frustrating	O
18,500	O
+1.9	O
58.70	O
workplaces	O
weighed	O
arrangements	O
LONDON	I-LOC
2,496	O
partner	O
Sobral	I-PER
Beach	I-LOC
productivity	O
diets	O
Glimt	I-ORG
three-match	O
child-sex	O
9.68	O
Aime	I-PER
Sabotzik	I-PER
Eternit	I-ORG
nevertheless	O
Spring	I-LOC	O	I-PER
ravine	O
wreckage	O
stores	O
10.28	O
10.29	O
standings	O
interim	O
Fourth	I-MISC	I-ORG
PARAMARIBO	I-LOC
flashlight	O
reformer	O
5.602	O
Victoria	I-LOC
289	O
288	O
Heike	I-PER
delegations	O
281	O
280	O
283	O
282	O
285	O
284	O
reformed	O
gmt	O
resolved	O
Mistr	I-PER
phenom	O
+2.3R	O
displaced	O
like	O
success	O
admitted	O
Durham	I-ORG	I-PER
Anders	I-PER
Above-normal	O
hair	O
Meligeni	I-PER
recommendation	O
Chenab	I-LOC
hurricane	O
Aalst	I-ORG
22,434	O
MINNETONKA	I-LOC
+0.2	O
+0.1	O
+0.0	O
+0.7	O
Baker	I-ORG	I-PER
Lichtwer	I-ORG
Japan	I-LOC	I-ORG
tomb	O
introduced	O
Lusaka	I-MISC
Iraqi	I-MISC	B-MISC	I-ORG
female	O
bowlers	O
1630	O
1631	O
rushed	O
Jablonec	I-ORG
Therapy	I-ORG
Jonathon	I-PER
November	O
insurer	O
sequel	O
Movladi	I-PER
8.25	O
8.26	O
BATISTUTA	I-PER
Doetinchem	I-LOC	I-ORG
underpriviledged	O
replying	O
+0.9;+23.6	O
periods	O
shoot-out	O
commentators	O
identities	O
Adams	I-PER
corporation	O
Zhilan	I-PER
detail	O
detain	O
drugs	O
Keiron	I-PER
Mamiit	I-PER
April	O
Deere	I-PER
stirred	O
Alba	I-ORG
DIARIO	I-ORG
Communist	I-MISC	I-ORG
Asselman	I-PER
undisputed	O
344	O
345	O
340	O
warplanes	O
@	O
vastly	O
Richter	I-PER
Exeter	I-ORG
school	O
MONEY	O
21-1	O
Boutoille	I-PER
guidelines	O
direct	O
umbrella	O
Mugabe	I-PER
blue	O
Stenning	I-PER
hide	O
Z$	I-MISC
selected	O
supplied	O
supplier	O
supplies	O
Fokker	I-ORG
licences	O
luggage	O
leaves	O
30-share	O
FOURTH	O
settled	O
midway	O
Group	I-ORG	O
Pedersen	I-PER
KUALA	I-LOC
now-destroyed	O
Poruri	I-PER
would	O
tenders	O
princess	O
distributing	O
spike	O
DOCUMENT	O
Glenallen	I-PER
ferrying	O
Tadayuki	I-PER
Litmanen	I-PER
Feugill	I-PER
excellent	O
NIDA'A	I-ORG
Tallinna	I-ORG
Crown	O
grenade	O
estate	O
paparazzi	O
Iraq-bound	I-MISC
attract	O
returned	O
ceremony	O
finalist	O
ONE	O
toxic	O
Eritrea	I-LOC
Marial	I-PER
description	O
Chiate	I-PER
Wilhelmina	I-PER
notionally	O
parallel	O
provisionally	O
amid	O
pullout	O
upside	O
Rouge	I-ORG
Gabriela	I-PER
Gabriele	I-PER
Woodruff	I-PER
TOTAL-	O
40.	O
+168,130	O
multidisciplinary	O
Miroslav	I-PER
406	O
16.4	O
400	O
nine-hitter	O
bails	O
16.8	O
diseases	O
prevented	O
Rowland	I-PER
3-146	O
Maigret	I-PER
herald	O
40s	O
consolidate	O
leftist	O
revisions	O
Vikstedt-Nyman	I-PER
laid	O
banning	O
newly	O
independence	O
associate	O
W	O
boosting	O
days	O
FORECAST	O
Surinamese-born	I-MISC
primary	O
fantasy	O
adopted	O
fact-finding	O
Congress	I-MISC	I-ORG
TRADE	O
77,719	O
confirming	O
+4.7	O
German-based	O
knife-wielding	O
Surrey	I-LOC	I-ORG
kidnaps	O
immigrants	O
Hilal	I-PER
seminal	O
2-2	O
Help-wanted	O
Teixeira	I-PER
Bernini	I-PER
seminar	O
traditionally	O
ENHANCEMENTS	O
Rev.	O
thorough	O
apartheid-era	O
96.0	O
2.96	O
2.95	O
2.93	O
2.92	O
Jaffna	I-LOC
2.99	O
milkman	O
GmbH	I-ORG
Fajardo	I-PER
accreditation	O
entertaining	O
NICE	I-LOC	I-ORG
pardoned	O
alight	O
Martinelli	I-PER
Chonan	I-ORG
analogue	O
5500	O
Udinese	I-ORG
spite	O
situations	O
Brumm	I-PER
542	O
543	O
Candiotti	I-PER
Finals	O
SIGN	O
PRESSURE	O
despite	O
Moore	I-PER
anxiously	O
Mediterranean	B-MISC
85,000	O
Emelia	I-PER
generally	O
Cruces	I-LOC
1960s	O
Textile	I-ORG
Formula	B-MISC	I-ORG
continually	O
firework	O
finger	O
hopefully	O
rebel-dominated	O
7.84	O
discovery	O
deposed	O
however	O
+167,330	O
Zimbabwean	I-MISC
news	O
Among	O
volleyed	O
fault	O
6.5-8.5	O
LM600	I-MISC
VEREINSBANK	I-ORG
expense	O
smuggled	O
conference	O
TVX	I-ORG
Kucera	I-PER
warehouses	O
TVM	I-ORG
captives	O
EXERCISE	O
Vermonter	I-MISC
Alexandra	I-PER
Alexandre	I-PER
Deputy	O
censors	O
marginalised	O
Praha	I-ORG
YMCA	I-ORG
Madagascar	I-LOC
3nb	O
Spokesman	O
Spar	I-ORG
Cordova	I-PER
Kaolack	I-LOC
Nieves	I-PER
forehead	O
Popullit	I-ORG
Springer	I-PER
peaks	O
numerical	O
buyback	O
Mudaba	I-PER
Prichard	I-PER
shortly	O
27,246.5	O
possessed	O
Velde	I-PER
Aaxis	I-ORG
WASIM	I-PER
Forma	O
Estonian	I-MISC
proposed	O
unemployment	O
Ulihrach	I-PER
proposes	O
grades	O
depart	O
Nuevo	I-ORG
STANDINGS	O
part-finance	O
outdueled	O
Deby	I-PER
gave	O
sidestepped	O
melting	O
breaks	O
Zitelli	I-PER
FEATURE	O
23.53	O
59	O
burnt	O
11,346,000	O
coxless	O
Slovan	I-ORG
Slovak	I-MISC
matchup	O
hunt	O
51	O
Curuchet	I-PER
election	O
peacemaker	O
contests	O
Edinburgh	I-LOC
Suan	I-PER
52.90	O
allocate	O
Milenko	I-PER
5,689.82	O
DOETINCHEM	I-LOC
brawl	O
rent	O
Melli	I-PER
attacks	O
plying	O
ensure	O
2,455	O
Kasparkova	I-PER
ppm	O
Environment	I-ORG
RATES	O
Gencor	I-ORG
139.3	O
Demel	I-PER
Selanne	I-PER
stuck	O
125.3	O
Herschelle	I-PER
Ames	I-PER
Amer	I-PER
Bread	O
26-29	O
payable	O
Giunluca	I-PER
semi-literate	O
GMT	I-MISC
eject	O
Marianne	I-PER
Von	I-PER
intra-day	O
MANAMA	I-LOC
Chonnam	I-ORG
Vnukovo	I-ORG
suspicions	O
0.60	O
Edouard	I-MISC	I-PER
sometime	O
0.65	O
0.68	O
0.69	O
regime	O
pledging	O
when	O
beheading	O
setting	O
papers	O
kerosene	O
1.875	O
picture	O
ropelines	O
football	O
flushed	O
1803	O
faster	O
1800	O
sacks	O
vigorously	O
trickle	O
rob	O
Santos	I-ORG	I-PER
deliveries	O
2:29.66	O
.01	O
.02	O
clarification	O
passage	O
Yoka	I-PER
newsprint	O
Regrettably	O
OctNov	O
sponsors	O
38.08	O
1.126	O
tanks	O
incitement	O
clouds	O
impressive	O
level	O
posts	O
cloudy	O
standards	O
domestically	O
differential	O
Tyndall	I-ORG
22,666.80	O
pork	O
tougher	O
trend	O
injunction	O
deflating	O
widened	O
Mayock	I-PER
bales	O
port	O
goes	O
VanLandingham	I-PER
Nov.	O
Papandoniou	I-PER
slaying	O
entertain	O
6-8	O
6-7	O
6-4	O
6-5	O
6-2	O
6-3	O
6-0	O
6-1	O
demolishing	O
rethink	O
AGENCY	O
Francesco	I-PER
Francesca	I-PER
Maine	I-LOC
Lees	I-LOC
problematic	O
Vicorp	I-ORG
Therefore	O
Huracan	I-ORG
prompt	O
Wednesay	O
crisis	O
3,420	O
3,422	O
prey	O
10,300	O
today	O
roared	O
These	O
Muenster	I-LOC
employed	O
Interacciones	I-ORG
cases	O
Gogele	I-PER
Barter	O
Sohail	I-PER
Stevanin	I-PER
Shikolenko	I-PER
nursing	O
figure	O
recover	O
48.96	O
choke	O
Adkins	I-PER
critic	O
mismanagement	O
vital	O
fourth	O
Demand	O
Macedonian	I-MISC	I-ORG
Opera	I-LOC
Tang	I-PER
Valero	I-ORG
Tana	I-ORG
PRICES	O
Pinas	I-PER
eighth	O
Gomez	I-PER
succeeded	O
Coal	I-ORG
Surinam	I-LOC
inform	O
syndicated	O
lamented	O
KELLY	I-PER
Aron	I-PER
Higher	O
Euromark	I-MISC
Rules	I-MISC
platform	O
farmer	O
loophole	O
Goinxha	I-PER
qualifies	O
qualifier	O
Supermarkets	O
qualified	O
obscene	O
Roma	I-ORG
donated	O
half-century	O
farewell	O
Petersburg	I-LOC	I-ORG
ZIFA	I-ORG
Prievidza	I-ORG
Wheat	I-ORG	O
tensions	O
Kensit	I-PER
Assoc	I-ORG
Stenhousemuir	I-ORG
Samsung	I-ORG
Guivarch	I-PER
CESKA	I-ORG
Felipe	I-PER
CESKY	I-ORG
Boca	I-ORG
turn	O
mortars	O
Speak	I-PER
grainbelt	O
well-oiled	O
cheerfully	O
Lidl	I-ORG
Commercial	I-ORG	O
14-man	O
W155	O
prosthesis	O
Havre	I-LOC	I-ORG
4-66	O
modelled	O
Knowsley	I-LOC
cards	O
questionable	O
42-3	O
Rangoon	I-LOC
batting	O
superman	O
Huisman	I-PER
resembling	O
Londono	I-PER
commonplace	O
Dealers	I-ORG	O
NUNTHORPE	O
donation	O
.411	O
.413	O
reconaisance	O
annum	O
Shopkeepers	O
proud	O
5-248	O
5-240	O
allegations	O
Research	I-ORG	O
spaces	O
Bundesbank	I-ORG
Saddam	I-PER
53rd	O
Louis	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
9373	O
jazz	O
Jiul	I-ORG
KNU	I-ORG
joked	O
Salim	I-PER
outperform	O
jokes	O
Geoff	I-PER
predicted	O
Ingwe	I-ORG
Shiraz	I-LOC
349,000	O
Scoreboard	O
Jaffray	I-ORG
slashing	O
1926	O
Todor	I-PER
managing	O
275,000	O
285-6	O
Gareth	I-PER
rumours	O
guitar	O
Krizan	I-PER
Himalayan	I-MISC
seven-year-old	O
acquiring	O
Colonna	I-PER
McMillan	I-PER
quiet	O
contract	O
Sameh	I-PER
Srebrenica	I-LOC
railway	O
Dahshour	I-LOC
Nabil	I-PER
HARD	O
period	O
insist	O
two-year	O
debt-service	O
IMF-sponsored	I-MISC
Lokeren	I-ORG
Ekeus	I-PER
direction	O
Madame	I-MISC
spirit	O
pilot	O
Jean-Michel	I-PER
cash	O
cast	O
1980	O
irrespective	O
abducted	O
Lauren	I-PER
Open	I-MISC	O
Opel	I-ORG
stabilising	O
Sierd	I-PER
refinery	O
leadoff	O
refiners	O
Glyn	I-PER
Kalashnikov	I-MISC
participant	O
author	O
granted	O
SIMEX	I-MISC	I-ORG
Nothstein	I-PER
status	O
81-7	O
Brechin	I-ORG
Jodie	I-PER
81-3	O
SunGard	I-ORG
ABABA	I-LOC
LEADING	O
Karak	I-LOC
Savicevic	I-PER
director	O
first-half	O
delicate	O
Banks	O
Dream	I-ORG
23,500	O
DIGEST	O
3,500	O
840M	O
Made	I-ORG
1,086	O
without	O
relief	O
inability	O
Forfar	I-ORG
bodies	O
ninth	O
cease	O
14.5-16.5	O
Belgian	I-MISC
Municipal	I-ORG
ETHIOPIA	I-LOC
lets	O
Many	O
soundly	O
Ortega	I-PER
Accompanied	O
Pioline	I-PER
Mano	I-LOC
parliamentarians	O
out-of-court	O
towed	O
wholly-owned	O
Bergmann	I-PER
tower	O
Kernaghan	I-PER
Petroleo	I-ORG
just-concluded	O
passers	O
DECLARED	O
competition	O
snatched	O
mood	O
frees	O
moon	O
GETS	O
freed	O
post-tax	O
slaughter	O
winningest	O
Forsyth	I-PER
Playing	O
gunshots	O
21,240	O
discussed	O
tribe	O
Arkansas	I-LOC	I-ORG
whales	O
there	O
alleged	O
988.2	O
380.6	O
resolute	O
cultures	O
alleges	O
fastball	O
Singer	I-MISC	I-PER
minimise	O
offical	O
wholesale	O
AUCKLAND	I-LOC
appellants	O
Subaru	I-MISC	I-ORG
Burundi	I-LOC
Coordination	I-ORG
pre-communist	O
20.37	O
taste	O
deserve	O
Dark	O
Panhandle	I-LOC
immunity	O
GABRICH	I-PER
mummies	O
START	O
Perelstein	I-PER
finals	O
Sachin	I-PER
Majesty	O
wife	O
Veldman	I-PER
Easley	I-PER
directors	O
treason	O
shortfall	O
Hendrix	I-PER
Leander	I-PER
anti-constitutional	O
Hendrik	I-PER
665M	O
cementing	O
meditation	O
research	O
decisions	O
Telfer	I-LOC	I-PER
apartment	O
Tikhomirov	I-PER
dairy	O
three-grade	O
Zeneca	I-ORG
559-mile	O
lawmakers	O
1-96	O
Tergat	I-PER
infringement	O
Alaska	I-LOC	I-ORG
mositure	O
treating	O
Pitesti	I-ORG
Steptoe	I-ORG
clinched	O
Testing	O
list	O
Carla	I-PER
Carlo	I-LOC	I-PER
Ilke	I-PER
negotiator	O
East	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG	O	B-MISC
Observation	O
risen	O
sum	O
brief	O
version	O
pulpit	O
row	O
Japie	I-PER
naval	O
Hueite	I-PER
65th	O
KHARTOUM	I-LOC
utilisation	O
Woolmer	I-PER
secondliners	O
horses	O
flat	O
Maso	I-PER
Morocco	I-LOC
Bilbao	I-LOC
Solskjaer	I-PER
Mass	I-MISC	I-LOC
Libyan	I-MISC
50,400	O
Basque	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
Lathwell	I-PER
Bloomsbury	I-ORG
Nepal	I-LOC	I-ORG
Thompson	I-PER
run-up	O
grey-haired	O
rather	O
occasionally	O
lighting	O
adventure	O
concentrating	O
contingency	O
proclaimed	O
Ciments	I-ORG
short	O
Belgrade	I-LOC	I-ORG
wallets	O
Kouame	I-PER
Roosevelts	I-PER
supervision	O
shore	O
Democrats	I-MISC	I-ORG
Simenon	I-PER
began	O
Kleinova	I-PER
Tarmac	I-ORG
Bianchi	I-PER
8.61	O
8.62	O
clashed	O
catchers	O
lobbed	O
clashes	O
Llaneras	I-PER
8.67	O
somebody	O
hunter	O
hunted	O
instructions	O
49,269	O
NEAGLE	I-PER
Pesalai	I-LOC
weight	O
Debre	I-PER
40,000	O
top-draw	O
Yelena	I-PER
disquiet	O
6-mth	O
SEYCHELLES	I-LOC
Epidemics	O
Arrivals	O
Hasan	I-PER
much-postponed	O
Opinion	O
3.385	O
Salamanca	I-LOC
bourgeoisie	O
Zhivkov	I-PER
.598	O
Blank	I-PER
.592	O
.594	O
.595	O
Tatiana	I-PER
Oklahoma	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
Territories	I-LOC
Indian	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
Taument	I-PER
.626	O
.627	O
story	O
"	O
.623	O
leading	O
interviews	O
porn	O
Bossi	I-PER
.628	O
Larry	I-PER
storm	O
store	O
Mohib	I-ORG
Hizbollah	I-ORG
rifle	O
king	O
kind	O
riyal	O
323-mile	O
Rokmeier	I-PER
+541	O
overran	O
1503	O
Taibe	I-LOC	I-ORG
Iceland	I-LOC
12,940	O
yogic	O
Hasely	I-PER
Levenson	I-PER
Six-month	O
fightback	O
RBA	I-ORG
4.6200	O
dealers	O
traditional	O
10-1-50-1	O
Sheffield	I-ORG	I-PER
lying	O
Florencia	I-PER
barter	O
Profit	O
stumped	O
fining	O
Suite	I-MISC
Mypa-47	I-ORG
Beatrix	I-PER
Bradys	I-PER
OFF	O
northerners	O
OFK	I-ORG
11-4	O
proces	O
11-6	O
11-1	O
11-3	O
11-2	O
11-9	O
11-8	O
adulthood	O
Kandahar	I-LOC
wrote	O
defense	O
Rosenborg	I-ORG
non-terminal	O
threats	O
coordination	O
Colchester	I-LOC	I-ORG
Ginola	I-PER
solo	O
Blackburn	I-ORG
sold	O
attention	O
confiscated	O
0.95	O
confiscates	O
oversee	O
bandit	O
operas	O
1,328	O
sweep	O
.542	O
19-man	O
regulated	O
village	O
Ibrahim	I-PER
Cement	I-ORG
Baronti	I-PER
flight	O
SLIM	O
demand	O
indefinitely	O
Donetsk	I-ORG
Kimiko	I-PER
2103	O
shortened	O
Moxon	I-PER
Vicenza	I-ORG
Semiconductor	I-ORG
demos	O
Serb-controlled	I-MISC
shirt	O
05/09	O
JACKSONVILLE	I-LOC
9	O
HUNGARY	I-LOC
prerequisite	O
higher	O
Supercoppa	O
restraint	O
SPOT	I-PER	O
cement	O
liquids	O
contractors	O
03/09	O
Hoechst	I-ORG
DINAMO	I-ORG
try	O
Zeng	I-PER
Socialists	I-MISC	O
historic	O
machinery	O
emerge	O
questions	O
JORNAL	I-ORG
prince	O
recapitalisation	O
Ironically	O
Wyludda	I-PER
9.4-1-45-3	O
2.19	O
Hands	I-PER
vetoing	O
2.11	O
2.10	O
Zyrecha	I-PER
Thou	O
advocate	O
sightings	O
M'bishi	I-ORG
Thon	I-PER
clemency	O
16.9	O
systematically	O
confront	O
AUTHORITY	I-ORG
separately	O
collect	O
Becanovic	I-PER
Richmond-based	I-MISC
Palmeiras	I-ORG
Eliahu	I-PER
Bacau	I-ORG
Prosecutor	O
Marek	I-PER
Robben	I-LOC
332.66	O
Katowice	I-ORG
Khadga	I-PER
refused	O
consolation	O
cautious	O
Ron	I-PER
putdowns	O
117.9	O
Roe	I-PER
lifeless	O
range	O
quashed	O
shake-up	O
Axworthy	I-PER
youthful	O
CONFIRMED	O
Kerkrade	I-ORG
Pavel	I-PER
LATE	O
inventories	O
strumming	O
impressed	O
EASE	O
lone	O
long	O
highest-ranked	O
Franklin	I-LOC	I-PER
Austin	I-PER
pro-life	O
lifespan	O
freight-tonne	O
fluctuations	O
OTC	I-ORG
Saxony	I-LOC
coordinator	O
three-stroke	O
Nazis	I-MISC
peace	O
Jorge	I-PER
backs	O
LOMBARDI	I-PER
MONROVIA	I-LOC
3.25	O
3.27	O
Eva	I-ORG	I-PER
3.29	O
nice	O
TNT	O
users	O
31.44	O
allowing	O
posters	O
happier	O
Edna	I-PER
119.6	O
departments	O
dragged	O
TAKE	O
Turner	I-LOC	I-PER
F.W.	I-PER
Based	O
alien	O
windy	O
gang	O
winds	O
uphold	O
15/9	O
Govett	I-ORG
breach	O
include	O
confirmation	O
left-footed	O
Rhodes	I-PER
P	I-ORG	O
Chesterfield	I-LOC	I-ORG
Spoerl	I-PER
Verstappen	I-PER
49.7	O
49.6	O
Telecommunications	I-ORG
concluded	O
gripping	O
Giampaolo	I-PER
makers	O
unavailable	O
Bamerindus	I-ORG
concessions	O
reappointment	O
bearish	O
19th	O
Former	I-LOC	O
degree	O
FRCD	O
Bulgarian	I-MISC
5,060	O
minor-league	O
Buyoya	I-PER
Semerdjieva	I-PER
Croatian	I-MISC
settling	O
Selection	I-ORG
larger	O
leaving	O
Joakim	I-PER
Palk	I-LOC
92.0-94.5	O
submerged	O
FLNC	I-ORG
Undersecretary-General	O
Orvieto	I-LOC
hardy	O
vols	O
from	O
Hiraki	I-PER
Illawarra	I-ORG
15-11	O
15-10	O
15-13	O
15-12	O
examination	O
15-14	O
constitutionally	O
timetable	O
15-18	O
vol.	O
Gul	I-PER
IBIS	I-MISC
parrots	O
Guy	I-PER
three-month-to-three-year	O
Brosius	I-PER
Dravid	I-PER
dissolve	O
thirsty	O
Alistair	I-PER
Australian	I-MISC	I-ORG
autobiography	O
syndrome	O
23.6	O
internationally-sponsored	O
struggled	O
toddler	O
fifth-inning	O
Noranda	I-ORG
wrist	O
Nuku'alofa	I-LOC
militarism	O
1886	O
majorities	O
Sairyu	I-MISC
six-year	O
reeling	O
trouble-makers	O
whilst	O
superior	O
holiday	O
crowds	O
campaigned	O
Ronaldo	I-PER
Joyner	I-PER
Janakantha	I-ORG
Turnover	O
articles	O
Machuca	I-PER
trimmed	O
Calderon	I-LOC
ambassadors	O
out	O
sentiment	O
chaos	O
indices*	O
frankness	O
Dianne	I-PER
59440	O
+358	O
+353	O
Agnes	I-PER
Markvart	I-PER
Dayton	I-LOC
footnotes	O
still-enslaved	O
bonnet	O
unknown	O
Fita	I-PER
Alloush	I-PER
656	O
657	O
1500	O
SPREAD	O
653	O
INDORE	I-LOC
RABOBANK	I-ORG
activists	O
startup	O
65M	O
diminish	O
7,391	O
Garang	I-PER
Rhineside	I-MISC
10-0	O
10-1	O
10-2	O
10-3	O
10-4	O
10-5	O
creditors	O
10-7	O
Remigino	I-PER
Diego	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
10,925	O
clip	O
Anton	I-PER
teenagers	O
M&R	I-ORG
POLLOCK	I-PER
Jody	I-PER
linked	O
ringed	O
Camerlengo	I-PER
WHEAT--Rains	O
Doce	I-ORG
patchy	O
Nunthorpe	I-MISC
who	O
why	O
Lindsay	I-PER
polyester	O
Morton	I-ORG	I-PER
skying	O
off-season	O
pipe	O
Everybody	O
agreed	O
Chemical	I-ORG	O
Sturrup	I-PER
feat	O
agrees	O
litigation	O
Veglio	I-PER
Dickson	I-PER
Shumer	I-PER
indignant	O
topple	O
GPG	I-ORG
burglars	O
malaise	O
Nicaraguans	I-MISC
ascertain	O
DEFLT	O
requirement	O
119.6**	O
1.13	O
favor	O
converted	O
crude	O
bought	O
conclave	O
2/94	O
opening	O
joy	O
Democrat	I-MISC	I-ORG
job	O
takeover	O
Citterio	I-PER
scoreless	O
Pretoria	I-LOC
Mets	I-ORG
Metz	I-ORG
Leoni	I-PER
Siow	I-PER
Playoff	O
tactical	O
grounds	O
unclear	O
Lila	I-PER
Expos	I-ORG
TITLE	O
soy	O
Thieves	O
symphonies	O
11,000	O
occured	O
swings	O
trademark	O
730	O
738	O
EMKAM	I-ORG
low-copper	O
Gastel	I-PER
Vale	I-ORG	I-PER
Ripken	I-PER
IRVINE	I-LOC
ensuring	O
last	O
stunning	O
medicinal	O
ringing	O
Spirlea	I-PER
thus	O
Mines	I-ORG	O
7.5	O
perhaps	O
overstayer	O
largest	O
difficult	O
Purdue	I-ORG
Caland	I-ORG
Todd	I-PER
rescision	O
BARCELONA	I-LOC	I-ORG
Paulinho	I-PER
Houston	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
correspondent	O
Lindholm	I-PER
Rome	I-LOC
undertaken	O
HAVING	O
ACCORD	O
excessive	O
heavily	O
Boulahya	I-PER
Deville	I-PER
Nicholas	I-PER
Eiden	I-PER
REDGRAVE	I-PER
arresting	O
usage	O
jars	O
Prusek	I-PER
Pearson	I-PER
provisions	O
Salah	I-PER
Salas	I-PER
Gabi	I-PER
press	O
PARTY	O
Sudradjat	I-PER
name	O
DOUBLE	O
exceed	O
smoothly	O
VTM	I-ORG
Sun	I-ORG	I-PER
flagrant	O
reclamation	O
Sui	I-ORG
employment	O
Biblical	I-MISC
ripped	O
Meluawati	I-PER
Jewel	I-MISC
doldrum	O
Patrik	I-PER
pasta	O
rare	O
carried	O
Jarmo	I-PER
carries	O
carrier	O
Americans	I-MISC
heroics	O
Angelica	I-PER
wilderness	O
Juan	I-LOC	I-PER
weather	O
promise	O
Russian-built	I-MISC
Finance	I-ORG	O
transfer	O
spiral	O
Amy	I-PER
Amr	I-PER
Champions	I-MISC
Guivarc'h	I-PER
volume	O
MANAGUA	I-LOC
automated	O
Consumer	I-MISC	O
Predrosa	I-PER
protesting	O
distract	O
Britain	I-LOC
cake	O
1740	O
12.442	O
+7095	O
Nunung	I-PER
83.40	O
Lufthansa	I-ORG
conclusion	O
Barrington	I-ORG
Shabwa	I-MISC	I-LOC
Arbroath	I-ORG
62,900	O
pumps	O
Karim	I-PER
Karin	I-LOC	I-PER
22.42	O
Sietco	I-ORG
tonnes	O
representative	O
writings	O
PREDICTION	O
yellow	O
Abbas	I-PER
prefix	O
Sundance	I-MISC
aegis	O
ornate	O
83,801	O
electricity	O
Casey	I-PER
20-6-70-2	O
Franny	I-PER
regional	O
7,032	O
prize	O
6-0-23-0	O
twenty-second	O
Chakravarty	I-PER
straight	O
95/96	O
charter	O
lock-out	O
Hradec	I-ORG
Hockey	I-ORG
Townsend	I-PER
unlisted	O
mixed-bloods	O
Poltava	I-ORG
Hooper	I-PER
increasing	O
Hingis	I-PER
Neville	I-PER
error	O
Budget	O
Stuttgart	I-LOC	I-ORG
Auchard	I-PER
Goalkeepers	O
Fashanu	I-PER
Hamas	I-ORG
Prykarpattya	I-ORG
Market	I-ORG	O
military	O
OAKLAND	I-ORG
Ikimi	I-PER
interferon	O
Compared	O
explained	O
2,355.93	O
PLAYERS	O
cheating	O
spoke	O
best-selling	O
fifth-	O
Brighton	I-ORG
Toronto-based	I-MISC
relay	O
successful	O
hurt	O
tying	O
hurl	O
Coordinate	I-ORG
chequered	O
Meghann	I-PER
famed	O
Enchaine	I-ORG
masterminds	O
artillery	O
ENDS	O
Brian	I-PER
RESTRICTS	O
BULLION	O
Holding	I-ORG
Czestochowa	I-ORG
Lloyds	I-ORG
Benoit	I-PER
complaining	O
handguns	O
damage	O
machine	O
methodology	O
Filippini	I-PER
Alcatel	I-ORG
destined	O
effective	O
wins	O
attracts	O
Serbia	I-LOC
PNW	I-ORG
Another	O
keeps	O
Manitoba	I-LOC
wing	O
wind	O
wine	O
Monterrey	I-ORG
Sigurd	I-PER
CBOE	I-ORG
1-16	O
CBOT	O
Prairies	I-LOC
rankings	O
Offered	O
extra-base	O
Harris	I-PER
hidden	O
Ruutel	I-PER
detachment	O
MRI	I-MISC
silver	O
represents	O
China-bound	I-MISC
APT	O
APA	I-ORG
interfering	O
financial	O
woes	O
Dortmund	I-ORG
250,000	O
fortnight	O
laboratory	O
Favourite	O
151-to-1	O
strategist	O
assured	O
University	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
fugitive	O
0.200	O
heading	O
build-up	O
Human	I-ORG	O
POISED	O
17.	O
17-	O
three-wicket	O
57.345	O
Tobago	I-LOC
wash	O
178	O
Quarterly	O
Ralf	I-PER
175	O
174	O
173	O
171	O
170	O
Cea	I-PER
engagement	O
listed	O
COLLATED	O
legs	O
listen	O
collapse	O
lumber	O
wisdom	O
predictable	O
sulphur	O
Beautiful	I-MISC
PHOENIX	I-LOC
point-by-point	O
Chaloner	I-PER
Meknes	I-ORG
endure	O
Gennadi	I-PER
bodyguards	O
seminary	O
Takeishi	I-PER
Angelo	I-PER
Angeli	I-PER
128.6	O
Angels	I-LOC	I-ORG
Williams	I-ORG	I-PER
concrete	O
Artmedia	I-ORG
60th	O
responsible	O
floating-rate	O
Baileys	I-LOC
Lixion	I-PER
causing	O
Banc	I-ORG
Russo	I-PER
Bank	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
even	O
Wisc	I-LOC
EDBERG	I-PER
looming	O
letter	O
retaining	O
drought	O
Nastja	I-PER
released	O
Repatriation	O
professor	O
Kingston	I-ORG
Semifinals	O
advisory	O
bomb	O
nominated	O
gauge	O
Northsea	I-ORG
theme	O
4.05	O
4.00	O
lenders	O
flanker	O
ever	O
Pescara	I-ORG
Emon	I-PER
avenged	O
flanked	O
Marsh	I-PER
blew	O
mandatory	O
disaster	O
fair	O
fail	O
best	O
score	O
Cage	I-PER
GRONINGEN	I-ORG
Volkov	I-PER
40.0	O
.511	O
.512	O
.515	O
.516	O
.519	O
NAGYATAD	I-LOC
PSI	I-ORG
violators	O
PSC	I-ORG
PSA	I-ORG
Jamaat-i-Islami	I-ORG
PSE	I-ORG
estates	O
federalism	O
5-365	O
PSV	I-ORG
pro-abortion	O
MainStay	I-ORG
25.	O
25-	O
irresponsible	O
active	O
258	O
259	O
Telegraph	I-ORG
252	O
250	O
251	O
257	O
254	O
255	O
contestants	O
criticised	O
extraction	O
Cesar	I-PER
Corrects	O
incompetent	O
41-5/16	O
life	O
Spiring	I-PER
Marino	I-LOC
hospitalized	O
Poland	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-PER
Jaafar	I-PER
lift	O
child	O
Siebens	I-PER
diverted	O
presidency	O
Hottiger	I-PER
Katarina	I-PER
Potsdam	I-LOC
On	O
Capital	I-ORG	O
Humayun	I-PER
cumulative	O
enlistment	O
babies	O
fairly	O
ringleaders	O
tops	O
Angeles	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
pioneers	O
Warhurst	I-PER
Anyang	I-ORG
5.75	O
J.J.	I-ORG
sectoral	O
subpoena	O
Russell	I-PER
Sjeng	I-PER
disguise	O
CONC	O
plight	O
ground-floor	O
Sobota	I-ORG
SNEAK	O
collections	O
13-month-old	O
TAKES	O
70,848.86	O
possible	O
firmer	O
possibly	O
birth	O
Missouri	I-LOC
unique	O
Grasu	I-PER
massively	O
OJ	I-ORG	O
new-found	O
seaside	O
steps	O
Abbaye	I-MISC
Hoiles	I-PER
Lillestrom	I-ORG
people	O
sure	O
Belcher	I-PER
warring	O
equestrian	O
sociology	O
for	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
10,756	O
Rabbani	I-PER
Saboteurs	O
FUTURE	O
Armenia	I-LOC
Keith	I-PER
Royce	I-PER
6,000	O
brokerage	O
pre-election	O
Hintum	I-PER
derailed	O
dollars	O
rebuffed	O
Bronson	I-PER
depopulated	O
Subpoenas	O
SOCIALISTS	O
reducing	O
one-time	O
Poznan	I-ORG
call	O
halls	O
happy	O
manufacturers	O
conclusively	O
2183	O
SLAM	O
prodcuts	O
Antioquia	I-LOC
army-controlled	O
peso	O
Engineering	O
Enrique	I-PER
panels	O
Amsterdam-Rotterdam	I-LOC
juvenile	O
looms	O
liberal	O
Variety	I-ORG
percolating	O
tournament	O
proven	O
exist	O
Bakker	I-PER
accounting	O
dealer	O
supporters	O
protested	O
actor	O
Hicham	I-PER
republic	O
2470.00	O
developers	O
3.25-3.75	O
maimed	O
Frana	I-PER
invested	O
Privately-owned	O
reorganization	O
sniffer	O
Indians	I-MISC	I-ORG
1948-52	O
532-8	O
Indiana	I-LOC
Verona	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
rousing	O
suspending	O
Fusai	I-PER
veterans	O
cheap	O
refinance	O
mourn	O
servicing	O
Seko	I-PER
Garrington	I-MISC
Springboks	I-ORG
Kalf	I-ORG
teak	O
Quigley	I-PER
subway	O
team	O
Tajikistan	I-LOC
prevent	O
1.48	O
Malbak	I-ORG
EARLY	O
current	O
Hengelo	I-LOC
mountainside	O
UNION	I-ORG
centime	O
Godwin	I-PER
Namibian	O
studied	O
wherever	O
Ecuadorian	I-ORG
crumbled	O
Prize-winning	I-MISC
studies	O
love	O
ipo	O
bloody	O
Alberto	I-PER
Hitleresque	I-MISC
capsized	O
Emanuele	I-PER
positive	O
predictions	O
anti-corruption	O
apparent	O
reprise	O
3-1/2	O
behalf	O
Kralove	I-ORG
4yrs	O
+34	O
valued	O
+31	O
+33	O
believes	O
values	O
believed	O
Our	I-LOC	O
Out	O
Federal	I-ORG	O
hides	O
winter	O
Vyacheslav	I-PER
Who	O
elephant	O
grossed	O
five-year	O
spot	O
P.V.	I-PER
applications	O
Jumbish-i-Milli	I-ORG
date	O
acceptances	O
data	O
sectors	O
Volkova	I-PER
wheelchair	O
sclerosis	O
11.34	O
Seismologicial	I-ORG
OVERS	O
Affleck	I-PER
Politehnica	I-ORG
Rawandouz	I-LOC
hiring	O
solitary	O
Maracaibo	I-LOC
hometown	O
SOCCER	O
decades	O
petition	O
militant	O
embezzling	O
matches	O
Socialist	I-ORG	O
330-member	O
Brunmayr	I-PER
Langer	I-PER
records	O
six-week	O
arriving	O
matched	O
Lalcher	I-PER
revert	O
Toomas	I-PER
Cloete	I-PER
bowling	O
113.02	O
113.00	O
revised	O
bovine	O
breakthrough	O
Jumet	I-LOC
low-wage	O
revises	O
NET	O
indexations	O
Jos	I-PER
Anwar	I-PER
298-6	O
contained	O
Joe	I-PER
suggesting	O
Jon	I-PER
bordering	O
Goncharova	I-PER
million	O
20th-ranked	O
possibility	O
UKCM	I-ORG
conman	O
Mixed	O
7149	O
disguised	O
Chavakachcheri	I-LOC
Money	I-ORG
RULES-AFL	I-MISC
2-57	O
scorers	O
3.50-4.00	O
Blanco	I-PER
vote	O
Blancs	I-ORG
Gains	O
indicate	O
2	I-MISC	O
Garlic	O
Hanmer	I-LOC
Iraq-U.N.	I-MISC
prone	O
29/8/96	O
150.3	O
29,434	O
Veritas	I-ORG
representing	O
High-priced	O
rival	O
VMIG	O
Alejandro	I-PER
future	O
prospect	O
Molde	I-ORG
Inquiry	O
lurking	O
Unsecured	O
BOTH	O
anti-graft	O
Jewish	I-MISC	B-MISC
Zelic	I-PER
taka	O
take	O
altered	O
Montserrat	I-LOC
Israeli-PLO	I-MISC
Separately	O
Belim	I-PER
Trainer	O
Portuguese	I-MISC
Portuguesa	I-ORG
inched	O
infections	O
AK-47	I-MISC
refining	O
Strip	I-LOC
forecasters	O
Blue	I-ORG
walking	O
surplus	O
Ferenc	I-PER
GILT	O
fibre	O
Sacramento	I-PER
Sierakowice	I-LOC
hockey	O
posted	O
clawing	O
Earthquake	O
bridge	O
Products	I-ORG
Madsen	I-PER
Mamedov	I-PER
bombs	O
JERUSALEM	I-LOC	I-ORG
neutralise	O
16th	O
raged	O
25-YEAR	O
surgery	O
diver	O
wielding	O
Mather	I-ORG
affecting	O
Primakov	I-PER
Quac	I-PER
scrutinise	O
supermarket	O
Fryman	I-PER
undermine	O
Kolumbina	I-PER
expression	O
twin	O
231-7	O
centralised	O
combines	O
booms	O
Yekaterina	I-PER
vacation	O
breath	O
combined	O
Mehmet	I-PER
Torrence	I-PER
Davies	I-PER
Greatest	O
two-goal	O
Kamiel	I-PER
Organisations	O
Trincomalee	I-LOC
Machado	I-PER
13.8	O
FEES	O
13.6	O
3-0-24-1	O
13.4	O
13.0	O
Rios	I-PER
coconuts	O
two-year-old	O
Fatkoullina	I-PER
NEUCHATEL	I-ORG
I	O
cheers	O
Iron	I-MISC
Nkgowe	I-PER
cheery	O
psychiatrists	O
vacant	O
costs	O
fixing	O
Botswana	I-LOC
Daniel	I-PER
non-binding	O
Judith	I-PER
weekly	O
Radnicki	I-ORG
Devereaux	I-PER
Harvest	O
Muller	I-MISC	I-PER
skies	O
Hitchcock	I-PER
Necmettin	I-PER
Jenson	I-PER
12-1	O
Ochieng	I-PER
6-	O
Wellman	I-ORG	I-PER
Mons	I-PER
+7.3;-3.6	O
62	O
full-scale	O
clay	O
64	O
series-clinching	O
grouping	O
sack	O
Dubrovshchik	I-PER
67	O
PHILIPPINE	I-MISC
21-day	O
racial	O
LKS	I-ORG
Cecchini	I-PER
last-place	O
Numerous	O
tube	O
Julius	I-PER
900.00	O
Partition	I-LOC
poise	O
Ripley	I-PER
industry	O
Scientist	I-ORG
act	O
gesturing	O
curling	O
flawed	O
image	O
parties	O
Pakistani	I-MISC	I-LOC
CARLSBAD	I-LOC
technically	O
JYVASKLYA	I-LOC
hookers	O
DRAW	O
mammals	O
brain	O
Invitation	O
Versfeld	I-LOC
Museeuw	I-PER
Guide	I-ORG
buying	O
79.9	O
Close	O
politically	O
agree	O
detailed	O
gone	O
ad	O
am	I-ORG	O
al	I-MISC
an	O
as	O
at	I-ORG	O
Auxerre	I-ORG
Komarica	I-PER
Kurdish	I-MISC	I-ORG
Phil	I-PER
2,700	O
explusion	O
COLONNA	I-PER
Edberg	I-PER
Cuthbert	I-PER
Gramoz	I-PER
videotape	O
original	O
Canada	I-LOC	I-ORG
Felicia	I-PER
9/16	O
Caesar	I-PER
LJUBLJANA	I-LOC
Tartous	I-LOC
Cameroon	I-LOC
improperly	O
careful	O
pornographic	O
Teplice	I-ORG
case	O
fruit-throwing	O
72-year-old	O
135-9	O
76th	O
Wolf	I-LOC	I-PER
offal	O
condition	O
accompanying	O
Bernabeu	I-LOC
scrapping	O
Ismail	I-PER
LOOS	I-ORG
antibiotic	O
penalties	O
All-Ordinaries	I-MISC
Tafawa	I-ORG
situated	O
Immaculate	O
section	O
nurse	O
installations	O
Notice	O
vomiting	O
hours	O
Roberston	I-ORG
4:14.784	O
round-trip	O
re-examined	O
backlash	O
Zurich	I-LOC	I-ORG
compliance	O
pick	O
action	O
Jared	I-PER
smuggle	O
Aug	O
Yekaterinburg	I-ORG
Kombouare	I-PER
coercion	O
850	O
852	O
853	O
Peat	I-ORG
Balkan	I-LOC	I-ORG
859	O
archives	O
pitching	O
87.45	O
Financing	I-ORG
Philippines	I-ORG
spoils	O
34-48	O
4,325-acre	O
logging	O
ARGENTINE	I-MISC
keeping	O
indicating	O
Conference	I-MISC	I-ORG
Micromation	O
stated	O
51.80	O
neglected	O
accept	O
states	O
STEP	O
Wijffels	I-PER
2,891.00	O
sense	O
Laban	I-PER
Venezuelan	I-MISC
information	O
Tacis	I-MISC
Fulham	I-ORG
earnings	O
Chandraratne	I-PER
Hanover	O
countryside	O
Villeneuve	I-PER
RAIN	O
Soundview	I-ORG
Swiss	I-MISC	I-ORG
backyard	O
9-2-26-1	O
acquisitions	O
Bongo	I-PER
KIGALI	I-LOC
Bastia	I-ORG
Nani	I-PER
rottweiler	O
Celopek	I-LOC
Nano	I-PER
Nana	I-PER
currrent	O
Benjamin	I-PER
Serbs	I-MISC
deeds	O
Padres	I-ORG
travelling	O
66.60	O
skipped	O
Stomil	I-ORG
propose	O
Alsthom	I-ORG
skipper	O
Gerhard	I-PER
Andrejez	I-PER
always	O
DeFreitas	I-PER
IPO	I-ORG
BATKIVSHCHYNA	I-LOC
Pole	I-MISC
Ata-ur-Rehman	I-PER
Poll	O
Destinations	O
week	O
85th	O
MANCHESTER	I-LOC	I-ORG
bouquets	O
Physicians	I-ORG
missed	O
BME	I-ORG
ministerial	O
highway	O
1920s	O
sparked	O
Hamid	I-PER
arable	O
Guingamp	I-ORG
0.275	O
bumped	O
Kirzan	I-PER
Bankruptcy	O
Kontogiannis	I-PER
slipped	O
gendarmes	O
number	O
Corruption	I-ORG
pledge	O
heads	O
symbolised	O
Courier	I-PER
threatening	O
heady	O
checkpoint	O
erupted	O
65,345	O
straight-set	O
relationship	O
immediate	O
appreciation	O
consult	O
focusing	O
grace	O
m;+21.5yr	O
determined	O
marriage	O
best-of-three	O
Gutters	I-PER
Fourth-placed	O
fights	O
391-seat	O
RUN-OUT	O
Cluj	I-ORG
CRICKET	O
Club	I-ORG	O
Archbishop	O
play	O
20-year-old	O
plan	O
defections	O
Americast	I-ORG
cover	O
Wodzislaw	I-ORG
attacking	O
defoliant	O
session	O
Alvarado	I-PER
impact	O
230-1	O
rbls	O
condos	O
failed	O
bastion	O
Atteveld	I-PER
Prime	O
Masters	I-MISC
Prima	I-ORG
LIFTS	O
actions	O
closely	O
Hearts	I-ORG
Pereira	I-PER
SHARPSHOOTER	O
Held	I-PER
low-fat	O
Craig	I-PER
set	O
ser	O
For	O
BRINGS	O
Fox	I-ORG	I-PER
sex	O
Foe	I-PER
see	O
migration	O
sea	O
Umm	I-LOC
muted	O
Paulo-Santos	I-ORG
Lauderdale	I-LOC
Belinda	I-PER
Freedom	I-ORG
325-350	O
Servet	I-PER
Florida	I-LOC	I-ORG
1,037	O
Dmitry	I-PER
Birnberg	I-PER
Kluivert	I-PER
Gouda	I-LOC
scams	O
goverment	O
whole	O
Kuhn	I-PER
drunk	O
WARRANTS	O
corresponds	O
community	O
hollow	O
Montgomerie	I-PER
agents	O
Hovercrafts	O
acceptance	O
THIRST	O
21-DAY	O
drink-driving	O
Krejner	I-PER
firm	O
fire	O
fund	O
towns	O
judicial	O
Anxieties	O
3,800	O
Stiajkina	I-PER
Concern	O
owed	O
142-4	O
Millwall	I-ORG
3432	O
2030	O
resulting	O
Oljeselskap	I-ORG
ingot	O
levels	O
Whittingham	I-PER
recent	O
FISCAL	O
Woodbridge	I-PER
Rate	O
SIGNS	O
Filipovic	I-PER
AUSTRALIAN	I-MISC
clearance	O
red-haired	O
THREE	O
Krpaco	I-ORG
plagued	O
Dragomir	I-PER
Virieu	I-ORG
anti-drug	O
U.N.	I-ORG
pillars	O
location	O
homeland	O
76.6	O
PORTO	I-LOC	I-ORG
victims	O
demands	O
Ramprakash	I-PER
flare-up	O
clutched	O
Osmond	I-PER
DES	I-LOC
DEM	I-MISC
sight	O
Damm	I-PER
109.4	O
sound-track	O
blood-red	O
+4.2R	O
Lajos	I-PER
be	O
Looi	I-PER
Riviera	I-LOC
agreement	O
Antonio	I-PER
by	O
anything	O
Rostislav	I-PER
ambush	O
Xhosa	I-MISC
ACC	I-ORG
well-organised	O
Pells	I-PER
Mid-tier	O
Young	I-ORG	I-PER
Larbi	I-PER
9.93	O
primarily	O
16.13	O
390	O
Nitra	I-ORG
Sciandri	I-PER
specifically	O
occupy	O
BONN	I-LOC
relaxed	O
Steady	I-PER
pastor	O
vowing	O
9.20-9.40	O
link	O
10.11	O
10.10	O
10.13	O
10.12	O
10.15	O
10.14	O
MED	I-LOC
Bhutto	I-PER
redeemed	O
MEN	O
lb-11	O
Prodi	I-PER
lb-12	O
1.209	O
nationalist	O
defined	O
overland	O
Tauranga	I-LOC
1.206	O
Parke	I-PER
Manhattan	I-LOC
107.0	O
41.4	O
Willison	I-PER
650,000	O
ASKED	O
worsened	O
miles	O
rescued	O
walked	O
summit	O
12.10	O
SUPER	I-MISC	B-MISC	O
12.19	O
CPI	I-MISC	O
code	O
CPN	O
results	O
37,000	O
shrugged	O
ORDERS	O
17,024,000	O
Milhaud	I-PER
send	O
McAllister	I-PER
citing	O
sent	O
Ansgar	I-LOC
garden	O
Goldstein	I-PER
BANKA	I-ORG
paratroop	O
Almere	I-LOC
categories	O
second-round	O
Talking	O
Boetsch	I-PER
Seattle	I-LOC	I-ORG
123,394	O
Stephanopoulos	I-PER
index	O
Yuan-dong	I-PER
HEADBUTT	O
Alan	I-PER
Balkans	I-LOC
Liwaya	I-PER
firms	O
bird	O
led	O
six-member	O
leg	O
lei	O
79th	O
shockwaves	O
les	I-ORG
let	O
leu	O
physiology	O
Streak	I-PER
engage	O
Energy	I-ORG
residents	O
Staff	I-ORG	O
Mountain	I-LOC	I-ORG
339	O
338	O
334	O
33.	O
F-14	I-MISC
standing	O
ministers	O
stakeout	O
doubt	O
occurred	O
Gump	I-MISC
sharply	O
Gumy	I-PER
insists	O
drill	O
Winger	O
high	O
BOLSWESSANEN	I-ORG
Several	O
McLaren	I-MISC	I-ORG
213,989	O
Clayton	I-PER
animal	O
Zarins	I-PER
blocks	O
Garcia	I-PER
Xamax	I-ORG
Ingrid	I-PER
jumpstart	O
shuffled	O
Community	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
selectors	O
acquitted	O
allow	O
intellectuals	O
Regina	I-PER
Kaiser	I-ORG
Match	O
Southeastern	I-LOC
spoiling	O
designs	O
Excluding	O
TOKYO	I-LOC
Katayama	I-PER
installment	O
Zaporizhya	I-ORG
Sporting	I-ORG
merge	O
kph	O
rising	O
02/09	O
BUSINESS	I-ORG	O
McEwen	I-PER
Mills	I-ORG	I-PER
Gynt	I-MISC
Interfax	I-ORG
intangible	O
Treasury	I-ORG
FUN	O
agriculture	O
goalkeeper	O
Agreement	I-MISC
KinderCare	I-ORG
reformist	O
Statesman	I-ORG
RELATIONS	O
Freddy	I-PER
machismo	O
HINCHCLIFFE	I-PER
Aides	O
blown	O
HOSPITALIZED	O
455	O
owned	O
straining	O
45.	O
6-iron	O
owner	O
buoyed	O
legislative	O
3,225	O
state-controlled	O
painful	O
adopts	O
lingered	O
tuscan	O
steel	O
colleagues	O
buttocks	O
tortured	O
briefing	O
steep	O
steer	O
spelled	O
Ong	I-PER
blockbuster	O
Agyepong	I-PER
clearly	O
prohibits	O
documents	O
Hartson	I-PER
28-36C	O
mechanism	O
demolished	O
soap	O
soar	O
Kronfeld	I-PER
Lybrand	I-ORG
Nikolaus	I-PER
HOLD	O
medal	O
green-and-yellow	O
Checker	I-ORG
Under	O
asylum	O
Independence	I-MISC
promote	O
planted	O
Tychy	I-ORG
secretaries	O
hope	O
exchanged	O
1986-87	O
quartering	O
Fringer	I-PER
exchanger	O
exchanges	O
River	I-LOC	I-ORG
committees	O
streamlined	O
rein	O
Lausberg	I-PER
Afghanistan	I-LOC
Sparta	I-ORG
19,560	O
edition	O
bidders	O
Harte	I-PER
Hannes	I-PER
partisan	O
NINE	O	I-PER
BALLANGER	I-PER
74-year	O
Jean-Pierre	I-PER
Edgbaston	I-LOC
Millns	I-MISC	I-PER
historians	O
restrictions	O
TRACK	O
drug	O
32.8	O
figures	O
32.0	O
nevus	O
32.5	O
32.7	O
Vaughan	I-PER
adjusted	O
cm	O
authorised	O
Guinea	I-LOC
ca	O
576	O
574	O
9,800	O
javelin	O
Garry	I-PER
allocated	O
dazzling	O
thieves	O
hottest	O
recurring	O
Gen	O
rioting	O
Eleusis	I-ORG
80-seat	O
Haruchika	I-PER
2010	O
2012	O
maul	O
ripe	O
delaying	O
surprisingly	O
Gothenburg	I-LOC	I-ORG
Sakigake	I-ORG
Menendez	I-PER
highlighted	O
249.53	O
congratulations	O
inlaid	O
ball	O
2,342.0	O
forecasts	O
COUNTY	I-MISC	B-MISC
paving	O
655M	O
Julio	I-PER
Julie	I-PER
Julia	I-PER
command	O
legendary	O
Marcin	I-PER
Marcio	I-PER
7:51	O
Equivalents	O
afflicted	O
Bahrain	I-LOC
Georgiopoulos	I-PER
residential	O
sickened	O
realize	O
Hedaya	I-PER
BOLD	I-ORG
state-paid	O
taunt	O
Khattabi	I-PER
Likkason	I-PER
Aarau	I-ORG
YR-AGO	O
Westwood	I-PER
replacement	O
ADVANCE	O
indications	O
thief	O
Actor	O
unaudited	O
Dehaan	I-PER
ballot	O
transport	O
disbelief	O
avoid	O
Barros	I-PER
SOKOLOVSKA	I-ORG
benefitted	O
stage	O
gained	O
sister	O
Yosu	I-LOC
seeds	O
German-born	O
Pedro	I-PER
ex-div	O
booed	O
commitment	O
Opener	O
PERTH	I-LOC
British-based	I-MISC
off-speed	O
housing	O
Morinville	I-MISC	I-LOC
feedlot	O
pretax	O
naturally	O
function	O
Weld	I-PER
Inderjit	I-PER
Well	O
MING	I-ORG
delivery	O
construction	O
delivers	O
Balance	O
16.875	O
official	O
smooth	O
3mo	O
Orii	I-ORG
Bancomext	I-ORG
Jesse	I-PER
bearing	O
recognize	O
Riga	I-ORG
denote	O
Clinical	I-LOC
shepherded	O
Thome	O	I-PER
variety	O
10,655	O
23.02	O
Volume	O
Fagan	I-PER
Nicklas	I-PER
Xenos	I-PER
Last-minute	O
25.00	O
South	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
15.125	O
Dekker	I-PER
pension	O
1360	O
rural	O
consolidated	O
165	O
Lodge	I-PER
Chappell	I-PER
160	O
PHILADELPHIA	I-LOC	I-ORG
Muthiah	I-PER
League	I-MISC	I-ORG	O
geology	O
blanket	O
sellers	O
wagons	O
blanked	O
3,820,000	O
sex-abuse	O
newroom	O
indices	O
FAITH	O
Shevchenko	I-PER
29th	O
rebels--poll	O
VOLUME	O
established	O
1=.6421	O
Wicky	I-PER
pts	O
+	O
27-year-old	O
establishes	O
churches	O
Voinea	I-PER
pursuit	O
Jean-Claude	I-PER
Kiptum	I-PER
McGrath	I-PER
Dimitris	I-PER
celebration	O
balance	O
0.39	O
0.38	O
0.37	O
0.36	O
Tuesday	O
0.34	O
0.31	O
0.30	O
Bystanders	O
Rupam	I-PER
bettered	O
4x100	O
co-world	O
secure	O
chooses	O
reign	O
encamped	O
PAULO	I-PER
PAULI	I-ORG
1ST	O
mainland	O
post-handover	O
permits	O
Marxist	I-MISC
McCoist	I-PER
Teenager	O
Jesus	I-PER
boats	O
ordinary	O
Zealand	I-LOC	I-ORG
Janette	I-PER
receding	O
Tunisian	I-MISC
greet	O
supermarkets	O
nascent	O
green	O
CALCUTTA	I-LOC
Trust	I-LOC	I-ORG
devote	O
consent	O
6.7	O
6.5	O
6.4	O
6.3	O
6.2	O
6.1	O
6.0	O
mayor	O
6.9	O
Catholics	I-MISC
Jabali	I-PER
somewhere	O
Judge	O
CONDITION	O
then	O
them	O
affected	O
1345	O
they	O
Award-winning	I-MISC
1.00	O
1.03	O
1.05	O
Sforza	I-PER
1.07	O
1.09	O
2,901.48	O
excavations	O
derailment	O
Rainbow	I-ORG
councils	O
crimes	O
stronger-than-expected	O
rain-affected	O
bare-chested	O
CZECH	I-MISC	I-LOC
Wars	I-MISC
vessels	O
Eritrean	I-MISC
6,150	O
Cambridge	I-LOC	I-ORG
recovering	O
installs	O
quadrangular	O
prft	O
festival	O
Chemlon	I-ORG
obey	O
AIDS	I-MISC
Nestor	I-PER
Samper	I-PER
Escuredo	I-PER
Smiley	I-PER
SEATTLE	I-LOC	I-ORG
damaging	O
B	O
Arabised	I-LOC
Sep	O
Sea	I-LOC	O
Sen	I-LOC	O
solely	O
Romero	I-PER
manner	O
Boardman	I-PER
strength	O
Rosset	I-PER
Kankkunen	I-PER
Rumbek	I-LOC
400,000	O
Houying	I-PER
Bonk	I-PER
Sidi	I-ORG
Bonn	I-LOC
Schnell	I-PER
Olivier	I-PER
Bond	I-ORG	O
51.00	O
Makkawi	I-PER
MAPUTO	I-LOC
Bjorn	I-PER
accounted	O
160-200	O
briskly	O
Kiev	I-LOC	I-ORG
anti-abortion	O
7.2	O
7.3	O
7.0	O
7.1	O
dredger	O
mid-Norway	I-MISC
exclusivity	O
jam-packed	O
Brann	I-ORG
Janeiro	I-LOC
guidance	O
Republicans	I-MISC
dn	O
do	I-ORG	O
de	I-MISC	I-LOC	O	I-PER	I-ORG
da	I-ORG
25,000	O
du	I-MISC
Soviet	I-MISC	I-LOC
Hedblom	I-PER
Dally	I-PER
Armstrong	I-PER
irregularities	O
liberalising	O
IHC	I-ORG
+91-22-265	O
ANGELES	I-LOC	I-ORG
11,500	O
BUS	O
BUT	O
Impens	I-PER
tainted	O
orchestrated	O
accord	O
MITCHELL	I-PER
Bobkova	I-PER
Edgar	I-PER
Cochrane	I-PER
postponement	O
Loretto	I-MISC	I-LOC
42.0	O
packages	O
42.4	O
42.5	O
cop	O
cow	O
336.47	O
parries	O
Navy	I-ORG
requests	O
negotiation	O
Quirot	I-PER
eyesight	O
non-core	O
Electricity	I-MISC
stillborn	O
Board	I-ORG
beheaded	O
Castilla	I-ORG	I-PER
Vicomte	I-PER
.429	O
Memoires	I-MISC
.424	O
.425	O
.426	O
.427	O
.421	O
.423	O
Hillary	I-PER
Casagrande	I-PER
dozens	O
families	O
Vice	O
Maniema	I-LOC
physician	O
MAJOR	I-MISC
spasms	O
Worcester	I-LOC
Zealands	I-MISC
FERENCVAROS	I-ORG
Amoco-Yemen	I-MISC
voice	O
Rubin	I-PER
comparative	O
confirmed	O
patent	O
monarch	O
indictment	O
Mordechai	I-PER
raid	O
blames	O
rail	O
rain	O
7-2-24-1	O
Polonia	I-ORG	I-PER
blamed	O
McGriff	I-PER
Diplomats	O
Minn	I-LOC
1978	O
1977	O
1976	O
1975	O
1974	O
Mind	I-PER
1972	O
1971	O
1970	O
Paraguay	I-LOC
the	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG	O	I-PER
camps	O
Jemison	I-PER
DIEGO	I-LOC	I-ORG
0.100	O
2847	O
2843	O
Petr	I-PER
Surprise	O
adding	O
Topolcany	I-LOC
hills	O
27th	O
Slovenia	I-LOC
spread	O
transformed	O
Lankans	I-MISC
BayerVB	I-ORG
mocked	O
Messages	O
caps	O
barge	O
Gerard	I-PER
middle-distance	O
insurgent	O
noteworty	O
bpd	O
Zambian	O
Trading	I-MISC	O
Liaoning	I-LOC
security	O
starvation	O
23-3-112-0	O
6-440	O
Ihlas	I-ORG
Lee	I-PER
ransacked	O
comments	O
SELIKO	I-ORG
REGULATION	O
Les	I-ORG	I-PER
480,618	O
Siemerink	I-PER
Place	I-LOC
Canonica	I-PER
STANSTED	I-LOC
Enioukhina	I-PER
Lord	I-LOC	O
dilemma	O
Cur	O
Cup	I-MISC	B-MISC
2,343.00	O
pays	O
Make	O
delighted	O
PICKS	O
back-to-back	O
balanced	O
ELIZABETH	I-LOC
Measles	O
liquidated	O
fight	O
accordingly	O
150,000	O
crime-infested	O
post-match	O
responding	O
veiled	O
Ferreira	I-PER
private-sector	O
Younes	I-PER
Vogts	I-PER
Malta	I-LOC
evidence	O
Hector	I-PER
five-point	O
physical	O
weakened	O
negotiators	O
interested	O
unwilling	O
pro-rated	O
Commissioner	O
INDIANS	I-ORG
Renzo	I-PER
Wanrooy	I-PER
affidavit	O
together	O
reception	O
lineup	O
Arbil	I-LOC
global	O
Dundee	I-ORG	I-PER
Elephant	O
Kulti	I-PER
supposedly	O
zone	O
outplayed	O
Abdulsamad	I-PER
permanently	O
Rouser	I-PER
liability	O
anonymous	O
blast	O
bring	O
McNeil	I-PER
Global	O
KLADNO	I-ORG
Firestone	I-LOC
revolution	O
Sacchi	I-PER
PCT	O
PIVOTAL	I-PER
acrimonious	O
2-136	O
Markgraaff	I-PER
Lows	O
During	O
satisfy	O
supporting	O
explosion	O
Berri	I-PER
chicane	O
overseers	O
Berry	I-PER
20.00	O
appears	O
change	O
Delbruck	I-PER
Cynthia	I-PER
exiting	O
trial	O
Tilburg	I-ORG
6-0-28-0	O
retired	O
lending	O
9.12	O
16.98	O
rarely	O
remaking	O
resigns	O
Dembinski	I-PER
Tiger	I-ORG
live	O
Gdansk	I-LOC
Netanya	I-LOC
marginally	O
credulity	O
Mount	I-LOC
Hunte	I-PER
Babakova	I-PER
Jens	I-PER
incidents	O
VODNI	I-ORG
No-one	O
spy	O
ahave	O
expanding	O
subsidies	O
supremacy	O
spa	O
productive	O
bankrupt	O
Arguing	O
bonds	O
Vice-president	O
averted	O
Overmars	I-PER
10-0-44-1	O
Keep	O
flourish	O
3/94	O
nationalistic	O
12.95	O
explicit	O
12.92	O
progressively	O
fireball	O
Courtois	I-PER
embassies	O
tagged	O
Donaldson	I-ORG
Chi	I-PER
forfeit	O
33-26	O
cold	O
birds	O
Greater	O
acknowledge	O
Landing	I-ORG
window	O
Bodies	O
Grace	I-PER
halt	O
thrid	O
sweetened	O
MINNESOTA	I-ORG
half	O
hall	O
Marlene	I-PER
servant	O
Corretja	I-PER
...For	O
entirely	O
Sakti	I-ORG
KICK	O
en	O
fired	O
Guadalajara	I-ORG
28-inning	O
fires	O
et	I-MISC
Caroline	I-PER
FINAL	O
shown	O
opened	O
space	O
distributers	O
opener	O
receiving	O
viable	O
shows	O
inevitably	O
Mauritius	I-LOC
rebel	O
Hlasek	I-PER
Atletico	I-ORG
Galarraga	I-PER
inevitable	O
Guiana	I-LOC
Bavarian	I-MISC
Cooperative	I-ORG
promotion	O
Gen'l	O
Even	O
striking	O
Aguirre	I-PER
Asif	I-PER
Asia	I-LOC
comprised	O
comprises	O
impossible	O
forwarding	O
size	O
sheep	O
Diamond	I-ORG
sheet	O
silent	O
cost-effective	O
friend	O
Johansson	I-PER
mostly	O
Guus	I-PER
pelting	O
14-17	O
14-15	O
Inc.	I-ORG
first-team	O
2,563.16	O
fruits	O
lunches	O
Idriss	I-PER
correction	O
13th	O
Call	O
anger	O
Pachuca	I-ORG
Crawford	I-PER
veteran	O
seven-hitter	O
objective	O
Cronje	I-PER
Colombians	I-MISC
dungeon	O
Nacion	I-ORG
Markou	I-PER
Markov	I-PER
Mackie	I-PER
insulting	O
2230	O
Letitia	I-PER
Fifty	O
penned	O
dispersed	O
Oriole	I-MISC
Barnagar	I-LOC
tonnage	O
Jean	I-PER
geography	O
ratio	O
PENALTIES	O
proportion	O
222	O
Crohn	I-PER
Madhumalla	I-LOC
NATIONAL	I-MISC	O
Ahmad	I-PER
honours	O
revulsion	O
Severin	I-PER
homegrown	O
Settat	I-ORG
ROMANIAN	I-MISC
Florentine	I-LOC
Allen	I-PER
husband	O
concert	O
Estimates	O
whitewash	O
fanned	O
concern	O
tackling	O
106.375	O
Berlin	I-LOC
inquiries	O
justified	O
Shahid	I-PER
27.482	O
article	O
UNITED	I-LOC	I-ORG
talented	O
ballpark	O
Yigang	I-PER
comes	O
dispatch	O
forehand	O
COCU	I-PER
Buettner	I-PER
Vitor	I-PER
lawsuit	O
Lierse	I-ORG
60.00	O
punished	O
100.92	O
Romanian	I-MISC	I-ORG
exhaustion	O
517-km	O
shortages	O
Brentford	I-ORG
Hamburg	I-LOC	I-ORG
wounds	O
observers	O
1mo	O
4-0	O
4-1	O
4-2	O
4-3	O
4-4	O
4-6	O
developing	O
4-8	I-MISC
BREGANCON	I-LOC
editorial	O
sorghum	O
Reina	I-LOC
Feng	I-PER
Carrefour	I-ORG
soil	O
Dick	I-PER
Corsican	I-MISC
heels	O
11.4	O
media	O
11.7	O
11.0	O
Chart	I-ORG
Aussies	I-MISC
11.3	O
1=35.73	O
document	O
finish	O
Chiluba	I-PER
Renshaw	I-PER
fruit	O
trawler	O
tradition	O
mentally	O
Joining	O
O'Neill	I-PER
Madhusudan	I-PER
3-for-4	O
Malivai	I-PER
EPR	I-ORG
EPS	O
3-for-3	O
storming	O
touch	O
speed	O
revaluation	O
Sterling	O	I-PER
tirade	O
Barsosio	I-PER
6-33	O
9:30	O
treatment	O
complements	O
struck	O
momentum	O
real	O
hover	O
read	O
Phillip	I-PER
Iberfreight	I-ORG
pesetas	O
execution	O
lady	O
rear	O
fractionally	O
pounds	O
Barmasai	I-PER
Operation	I-MISC
Before	O
408-8750	O
BILLIONS	O
hacks	O
Archives	I-ORG
duration	O
Nyrere	I-PER
Galvez-Lopez	I-PER
15,613	O
recorded	O
conservative	O
2173	O
++359-2	O
Co-ordinated	O
credits	O
hectic	O
ONE-DAYER	O
Hyderabad	I-LOC
placard	O
S.A.	I-ORG
underway	O
superbike	O
deranged	O
Ratlam	I-LOC
She'an	I-ORG
protests	O
heated	O
operator	O
prepare	O
stoppage	O
5-0-24-0	O
Hotel	O
genetic	O
Birthday	O
one-dayers	O
cottage	O
Calcutta	I-LOC
trying	O
circulation	O
comics	O
5/8	O
builders	O
Alucasa	I-ORG
moved	O
sales	O
moves	O
Jailed	O
Reading	I-ORG
Koeln	I-LOC
credibility	O
storage	O
782.6	O
Schering	I-ORG
Ghent	I-ORG
More	O
gaining	O
pundits	O
18-3-55-1	O
Eijden	I-PER
Estates	I-ORG
coverage	O
away-goal	O
66.74	O
doubted	O
Pablo	I-PER
69th	O
pointing	O
81,000	O
splitting	O
Moses	I-PER
Brown	I-PER
batches	O
FORCE	O
referring	O
Nirmal	I-LOC
airfreight	O
BODY	O
confidential	O
very	O
mph	O
austerity	O
Enzo	I-PER
underperform	O
20.036	O
Kruger	I-PER
Breakfast	I-ORG
3.19	O
opting	O
3.14	O
3.17	O
49,900	O
conscience	O
HUF	O
Latin	I-MISC
Latif	I-PER
three-game	O
witnesses	O
roofs	O
infamous	O
Bethlehem	I-LOC
multinational	O
recruits	O
answers	O
strong	O
Papua	I-LOC
ahead	O
soldier	O
Eijkelkamp	I-PER
Victor	I-LOC	I-PER
CeBIT	I-MISC
Bohemians	I-ORG
hogs	O
3,250,000	O
disposals	O
season-high	O
Ecus	I-MISC
ROME	I-LOC
Geert	I-PER
ROMA	I-ORG
injury	O
Penberthy	I-PER
TELFER	I-PER
SPORITELNA	I-ORG
Prieto	I-PER
broke	O
Containment	O
suction	O
hurry	O
CYPRUS	I-LOC
Oran	I-LOC
1415	O
Butare	I-PER
Wengert	I-PER
nine	O
Meditation	I-MISC
AVERAGES	O
Inflows	O
week-ago	O
pushes	O
Delahunty	I-PER
MASTERKOVA	I-PER
12.208	O
exclude	O
lacks	O
Dowman	I-PER
ASIA	I-LOC
foresees	O
rapists	O
ft	O
Eefje	I-PER
Fitzpatrick	I-PER
roadblocks	O
Syria	I-LOC
four-decade	O
fo	O
Fenerbahce	I-ORG
morphine	O
laminate	O
overnight	O
Grossard	I-PER
50-75	O
Fili	I-PER
Loznica	I-ORG
Derivatives	I-ORG	O
Aerostan	I-ORG
Africans	I-MISC
39,584	O
108,288	O
animist	O
273-5	O
fined	O
OFFICIAL	I-ORG	O
Cardinals	I-ORG
STRIKER	O
25.87	O
Tamil-speaking	I-MISC
fines	O
post-war	O
food	O
40-year-old	O
sweeping	O
WARSAW	I-LOC
well-known	O
HELIBOR	I-MISC
trailed	O
molotov	O
transplanting	O
heavyweights	O
die	O
referred	O
editor-in-chief	O
bickering	O
SLOVAK	I-MISC
Anjalonkoski	I-MISC
cemented	O
juniors	O
blue-chip	O
since	O
Multi-layers	O
1,461	O
dirt	O
Breda	I-LOC	I-ORG
Waalwijk	I-ORG
base	O
ask	O
third-busiest	O
Investments	I-ORG
uprooted	O
JOHANNESBURG	I-LOC
339.00	O
PAPENDRECHT	I-LOC
partnerships	O
Watanabe	I-PER
probability	O
reflected	O
elder	O
1873	O
1870	O
villa	O
herbicides	O
Nature	I-ORG
vice-chairmen	O
Sinead	I-PER
Sigeki	I-PER
Venture	I-ORG
Srinath	I-PER
Lancashire	I-ORG
MATCH	O
WELLINGTON	I-LOC
shacks	O
Defence	I-ORG	O
Saudis	I-MISC
TURKISH	I-MISC
Father	O
Current	O
substantial	O
Ezer	I-PER
post-1997	O
vulnerable	O
10-1-54-0	O
7-0-28-1	O
cargoes	O
labour	O
Horvath	I-PER
towards	O
BEAT	O
quote	O
quota	O
The	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG	O
salary	O
Coetzer	I-PER
Narino	I-LOC
Coetzee	I-PER
29.2-9-83-3	O
Norris	I-PER
667	O
666	O
662	O
+361	O
completion	O
Kiptanui	I-PER
heir-to-the-throne	O
1663/96	O
pretty	O
DEFEAT	O
Bolger	I-PER
meanwhile	O
custodial	O
trees	O
Crystal	I-ORG
Vanderbijlpark	I-LOC
during	O
1.82	O
1.84	O
left-wing	O
sacrificed	O
101.80	O
Douati	I-PER
Bombay	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
Riza	I-PER
transportation	O
Neither	O
Parc	I-LOC
Para	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
won	O
Cricuma	I-ORG
woe	O
Fighter	I-MISC
readying	O
5,486,000	O
SKODA	I-ORG
Harb	I-PER
Hart	I-PER
batters	O
1,143	O
motivation	O
badminton	O
likes	O
monies	O
doping	O
Woodforde	I-PER
described	O
unaided	O
Most	B-MISC	O
describes	O
maintenance	O
Gualtiero	I-PER
budgeted	O
partly	O
crack	O
08/26/96	O
Nawaz	I-PER
second-quarter	O
Whitlinger	I-PER
governor	O
Issuer	O
65-56	O
voters	O
Feldhoff	I-PER
overlooked	O
9.0-12.0	O
rulers	O
wartorn	O
Alert	I-ORG
Ujpest	I-ORG
Qasr	I-LOC
sham	O
used	O
temporary	O
Ottoz	I-PER
70.9	O
uses	O
Publications	I-ORG
plugs	O
677.98	O
Teutenberg	I-PER
clears	O
Giro	I-MISC
29th-ranked	O
Dennis	I-PER
Seitzer	I-PER
CINCINNATI	I-ORG
767	O
quarters	O
Fans	O
distanced	O
praying	O
Cimicchi	I-PER
$	O
sprinter	O
Football	I-MISC	I-LOC	I-ORG
guaranteed	O
sprinted	O
...	O
march	O
Olofsson	I-PER
Billa	I-ORG
tiring	O
Billy	I-PER
Biehl	I-ORG
Bills	I-ORG
paramilitary	O
submission	O
UBS	I-ORG
signal	O
strife	O
Learning	I-ORG
ABDERDEEN	I-LOC
brakes	O
imam-in-exile	O
4-90	O
creation	O
49-year-old	O
4-95	O
trends	O
Bugno	I-PER
fanfare	O
Pittsburgh	I-LOC	I-ORG
Ijaya	I-PER
NWE	O
pounding	O
slash	O
Kredietbank	I-ORG
run	O
Clontz	I-PER
first-time	O
processing	O
Amsterdam-Rotterdam-Antwerp	I-LOC
Tromso	I-ORG
Israel-PLO	I-MISC
abroad	O
162-4	O
faith	O
Scorers	O
76	I-MISC	O
Scac	I-ORG
Catherine	I-PER
Altun	I-PER
Lion	I-ORG
74	O
Quake	O
W125	O
seeing	O
SORRENTO	I-PER
RBI	I-MISC	I-ORG
Their	O
Racing	I-ORG
rolls	O
pro-Israel	I-MISC
5-217	O
consultation	O
Bestop	I-ORG
CATCH	O
Vitaly	I-PER
confessing	O
0-6	O
himself	O
0-0	O
0-1	O
0-2	O
Agrins	I-PER
Individuals	O
Spitzbergen	I-LOC
U.N.-sponsored	I-MISC
....	O
Murray	I-PER
Haarlem	I-LOC
inch	O
adults	O
languishing	O
victories	O
Acre	I-PER
cotton	O
Tavria	I-ORG
politicians	O
Speaking	O
67,000	O
forge	O
fast-moving	O
spectators	O
Orlando	I-PER
re-election	O
visits	O
1.4935	O
Airdrieonians	I-ORG
required	O
Matete	I-PER
depth	O
heats	O
requires	O
Lars	I-PER
kilometre	O
nuns	O
Lara	I-PER
go	O
116th	O
baron	O
Alcan	I-ORG
arid	O
government-owned	O
breakout	O
capturing	O
new-ball	O
portfolios	O
1791	O
extra-judicial	O
Itami	I-LOC
80th	O
defamatory	O
KOMERCNI	I-ORG
SepOct	O
Cetes	I-MISC
Guerrero	I-LOC
335.00	O
23-24	O
DENVER	I-PER
Boys	I-ORG
experiment	O
gloom-stricken	O
selecting	O
;	O
Swift	I-PER
300-seat	O
Bekila	I-PER
stance	O
Greer	I-PER
Greek	I-MISC
focused	O
Volumes	O
Arum	I-PER
115,000	O
+3,831	O
likened	O
Sung-Hee	I-PER
Jean-Louis	I-PER
1241	O
products	O
examining	O
Tanjug	I-ORG
Hindu	I-MISC
Piotti	I-PER
CHILLICOTHE	I-LOC
Explaining	O
Osterloh	I-PER
counties	O
reflects	O
1/3	O
1/2	O
Denmark	I-LOC
benchmark	O
1/9	O
missile	O
Claire	I-ORG
24.90	O
Akpoborie	I-PER
SNET	I-ORG
Tauranaga	I-LOC
GREER	I-PER
1994-95	O
escaped	O
GREEK	I-MISC
GREEN	O
documenting	O
founding	O
gains	O
Aoki	I-PER
Ijaz	I-PER
BVSC	I-ORG
71st	O
located	O
Gore	I-PER
MANILA	I-LOC
Corser	I-PER
chiefs	O
Boskalis	I-ORG
11-7	O
Farewell	I-MISC
agenda	O
healthcare	O
software	O
Gonzalez	I-PER
Smith	I-PER
offences	O
356,725	O
subversive	O
Rapeseed	O
Luis	I-PER
Gaissmayer	I-PER
sword	O
Miami	I-LOC	I-ORG
auto	O
Brother	O
hippies	O
Supreme	I-ORG	O
Celsius	I-MISC
mode	O
Vladikavkaz	I-ORG
upward	O
PRODUCER	O
aggravated	O
Dumbarton	I-ORG
1,184.0	O
18.40	O
scrum-half	O
Alonso	I-PER
activism	O
repositioning	O
7-year	O
activist	O
PKK	I-ORG
underpinned	O
Ducruet	I-PER
achievements	O
befriended	O
Rostselmash	I-ORG
route	O
keep	O
keen	O
Lama	I-PER
KANSAS	I-LOC	I-ORG
Rune	I-PER
Lamm	I-PER
Tamer	I-PER
Revs	O
Lamy	I-PER
Slavia	I-ORG
43.50	O
Klas	I-PER
Interviewed	O
20.81	O
attack	O
motorcyle	O
ASK	I-ORG
Obilic	I-ORG
Ozers	I-PER
2-0	O
2-1	O
2-6	O
2-7	O
2-5	O
earmarked	O
DUE	O
R	I-PER
Yihye	I-PER
Mapourdit	I-LOC
herself	O
Hegi	I-PER
outline	O
Grossman	I-PER
photograph	O
ultimatum	O
bed	O
Rohan	I-PER
staking	O
spurt	O
providing	O
Information	I-ORG	O
lightly	O
Highlights	O
unchanged	O
border	O
gunned	O
Urals	I-MISC
plugging	O
demise	O
2.240	O
consequences	O
proceedings	O
businessman	O
affair	O
Matt	I-PER
Mats	I-PER
Jadeja	I-PER
coal-mining	O
Mate	I-PER
parked	O
Stud	I-ORG
Pitkowski	I-PER
Chelsea	I-ORG	I-PER
15,704.3	O
50-year	O
fuel	O
slows	O
12.	O
120	O
122	O
124	O
125	O
127	O
128	O
129	O
Ieng	I-PER
shr	O
evident	O
Offerman	I-PER
shy	O
she	O
accuses	O
34.9	O
prayers	O
34.6	O
34.0	O
argued	O
accused	O
Jannie	I-PER
written	O
neither	O
128-1	O
sole	O
128-4	O
spared	O
squads	O
approval	O
interpretations	O
Strunz	I-PER
Headlines	O
SLIDE	O
Struggling	O
addition	O
discrimination	O
Immigration	I-ORG
.457	O
MOTOR	O
talent-laden	O
5,951	O
Fanie	I-PER
ISLAMABAD	I-LOC
expenditure	O
mail	O
kicks	O
Logistics	I-ORG
3,200	O
Rusty	I-PER
Commem	O
owns	O
Cyprus	I-LOC	I-ORG
resident	O
Yatchenko	I-PER
plundered	O
4.54	O
4.50	O
ing	O
PPI	O
17,166,000	O
non-debt	O
incumbent	O
fast-tracks	O
+1.5	O
Foreldorado	I-ORG
+1.0	O
transaction	O
Curren	I-PER
i	I-ORG
53112	O
KANKKUNEN	I-PER
MAKINEN	I-PER
accurate	O
Sunday	I-PER	O
low-level	O
pro-Baghdad	I-MISC
.549	O
.547	O
.545	O
.543	O
deposits	O
.540	O
Helmut	I-PER
7-1-24-0	O
warrant	O
kick	O
Yasser	I-PER
Ghibellines	I-MISC
definitive	O
fate	O
accompagnied	O
26.	O
260	O
267	O
266	O
264	O
269	O
prominent	O
7,149	O
renegade	O
Arazi	I-PER
controllers	O
Larkin	I-PER
oppreses	O
expansion	O
27,600	O
GUILDERS	O
Shinichi	I-PER
Mandolina	I-PER
sinister	O
recognizes	O
DALGLISH	I-PER
celebrations	O
Jobless	O
5.24	O
20,167	O
Micijevic	I-PER
Lazarek	I-PER
Lawrence	I-PER
noticed	O
Niclas	I-PER
accountant	O
CGT	I-ORG
79,390	O
hierarchical	O
Croatia	I-LOC
Daschle	I-PER
he	O
Industrial	I-MISC	O
77th	O
limit	O
overstayed	O
twist	O
SOLIDERE	I-ORG
referee	O
NICOSIA	I-LOC
Ally	I-PER
Dhiraj	I-PER
fledgling	O
Luo	I-PER
disposing	O
RTRS	I-ORG
Jongsma	I-PER
appoint	O
Avianca	I-ORG
Proposition	I-MISC
10,725	O
Buran	I-PER
Zwingmann	I-PER
protest	O
Lawrie	I-PER
4,420	O
jeopardising	O
fronts	O
Liverpool	I-ORG
Gwynn	I-PER
1980-88	O
Mystery	O
Kovacs	I-PER
rescue	O
activation	O
railways	O
flashpoint	O
reforms	O
affect	O
sidelined	O
post-season	O
companies	O
solution	O
Fasth	I-PER
cholesterol	O
MOODY	I-ORG	O
ups	O
Ancelotti	I-PER
clothes	O
favoured	O
Strasbourg	I-ORG
anti-Rangoon	I-MISC
NYC	I-MISC
colourful	O
Put	O
new	O
net	O
never	O
drew	O
Lillee	I-PER
Correction	I-ORG
golds	O
Meidlinger	I-PER
county	O
turning	O
drowned	O
strapless	O
27-4	O
neighbours	O
Wilkins	I-PER
recommend	O
N.J.	I-LOC	I-PER
type	O
tell	O
posting	O
shelters	O
4:15.006	O
rights	O
Choonhavan	I-PER
2.60	O
Klinsmann	I-PER
CALLS	O
give	O
stagnates	O
Humphries	I-PER
Toubon	I-PER
U.S	I-LOC
stupidity	O
Jack	I-PER
U.N	O
4,464	O
abdomen	O
05:30	O
Howell	I-PER
Banska	I-ORG
Prolific	O
6-0-29-1	O
Laurence	I-PER
Sharpe	I-PER
47.93	O
Brunswijk	I-PER
ISS	I-ORG	O
NORWAY	I-LOC
Rahman	I-PER
Bobby	I-PER
unemployed	O
academics	O
DAKAR	I-LOC
7-pound	O
rhetoric	O
Milan	I-LOC	I-ORG	I-PER
KABLO	I-ORG
daughters	O
STICH	I-PER
5,350	O
luck	O
interruption	O
57th	O
Dressed	O
About	O
taught	O
Ennea	I-MISC
dawn	O
enclosure	O
roadblock	O
decree	O
networked	O
122.5	O
Cascarino	I-PER
surprise	O
HMG	I-ORG
sluggish	O
Gippsland	I-MISC
11.04	O
11.00	O
FIXTURES	O
3.92	O
hickey-like	O
3.98	O
messages	O
impede	O
Rayyan	I-PER
loud	O
economists	O
executions	O
beta-1b	O
scrape	O
girls	O
mid-August	O
inflow	O
FINNISH	I-MISC
villages	O
No.3	I-ORG
No.2	O
No.1	O
swells	O
Post	I-ORG	I-PER
Galina	I-PER
matter	O
Colin	I-PER
N.M.	O
8/30	O
Floor	O
reprieve	O
soared	O
power-hungry	O
Kiernan	I-PER
Algerian	I-MISC
Dirkx	I-PER
64th	O
accurately	O
Anthuan	I-PER
Alexandrou	I-PER
medical	O
Philippine	I-ORG
Dynasty	I-MISC
points	O
Agadir	I-ORG
visitor	O
paceman	O
Kinkel	I-PER
Samson	I-PER
thirds	O
judges	O
Ballybunion	I-ORG
unleashed	O
Komala	I-PER
Pembroke	I-LOC
glaciers	O
stop	O
meditate	O
Palestinians	I-MISC
FIORENTINA	I-ORG
Johnstone	I-ORG
fields	O
95975	O
Anatoly	I-PER
briefed	O
ethical	O
reference	O
Dnipropetrovsk	I-ORG
Belle	I-PER
Ponting	I-PER
Debbie	I-PER
encephalopathy	O
